The cards laid out for show
Stars shining so bright
Watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
Dance to the mystery
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So, let the tarot move
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream be the callin and slurring words starting up the scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sikes twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama's podcast. This a runaway train
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob flashing on cam chat losing
in the chat but she ain't got time for a dude like that diamond flirting hard let the girls
react it's a freak show party no filter all facts yo all facts yo yo michael drops a line
gong not tonight alex tried to joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways someone's
gotta fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirt slipping down
But still cracking jokes slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow no rules just rolls
We pretend to play one hand on the mute of the letting it spray. It's a circus a riot a beautiful mess
One wrong word and we're trending in the press
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight
fashion on cam chat
Got the glasses. Hold on
I don't know but did I get it right? I don't know
I'm dumb rash I
Think my life has changed I'm there's a banana coffee
Ever had a banana coffee so good tricks is drinking the whipped cream stop fix them
They the whipped cream is like really sweet
The coffee is really bitter it's so good
Mmm, I got that and I got a salted caramel and like a big drink
But this is a banana coffee, this is a banana iced coffee, it's so good.
We have a lot of good Vietnamese, good Vietnamese places around here.
You know, unfortunately this banana vapes, yeah.
I love the taste of it.
Banana is a great taste, you know, I don't know.
I think bananas get a bad rap, maybe.
It's easy, I think.
Okay, so I know what I did.
I made the text too big.
Okay, so how do I just put the pixels?
Okay, let me see.
Let me make it small. Let me see. Accessibility. Okay.
This should work better. Let me see. Oh! Hey, Ghost! Thank you. Thank you, Ghost. Wow. Thanks so much.
$20 guys. Thank you so much goes. Wow
It's very extremely generous and I really appreciate you. Thank you so much
Yeah, so what do you guys like them, I think
okay, I
Know I kind of like a little bit like
It kind of like I kind of mixed like the black frames with like, you know
I kind of like kind of thick nerd frames kind of but then
Like they have like the aviator kind of style.
I don't think, I don't think it's good.
I think kind of like scary, scary.
Wow, ghosts.
Yeah.
Okay.
Don't knock over my coffee.
Like, Tricks is drinking like the whipped cream.
Okay, I'm gonna go.
So guys look here. I'll show you a little bit of my kitchen. It's a little bit. It's cleaner now. See I have some bottle of alcohol
It's a little bit. It's not a little bit messy, so okay, so it's all you're gonna see. I'm gonna see my kitchen
I don't need to let my, let me see. Oh, let me see. I got all the way back from the
liquor store today, and then I like lit my cigar and the lighter was out. Could you believe it?
So I have to like light it on the stove all night
Whoa hold on oh
Arbiter whoa
Thank you the ghost
The ghosts with the most
Thank you
Definitely are awesome guy. I'm gonna fix the text again. So I'm like even smaller
So I have my big glasses now so I can actually read it
Settings accessibility there we go
Yeah, it helps. Oh my gosh. Now I can see all the comments. They're really small now, but
Jeffrey Dahmer eats a case five. Who said that Cyrus? Come on. Yeah, the panel's open. I think I
You're a nerd. Yeah, I love ghosts
But uh, what a nice surprise. Thank you so much ghosts
Here we go
Yo, yo, I
Looks like you. Hi. Thank you girls. Did I mention that beard is working and I mentioned your glasses. They're giving
You like it?
I like you brother. Okay. I think they're a little bit of like they're a little bit
Hey, don't say yourself too much, but I like it
Thank you
Well, I uh, yeah, I really you know, I thought these were appealing and they're
Interesting is a little bit strong, but thank you so much. They don't allow anybody to see what do not shows anymore because of the way
I don't want to sponsor any channels or nothing like that when we pick anybody. It's your money. You do whatever you want with it
Thank you girls
Yeah
Pretty generous and very much appreciate it. I will make sure
Shout you out and you know, I won't forget that. Thank you so much
Yeah, so there's no need like you. There's no need to kick me out or nothing like I don't I know I know I am
Asshole sometimes though. I am an asshole sometimes you got a little bit mean to
Mean to some people. Yeah, we see my if you see my alien
Yeah, nice. Oh god. Oh nice
Spunky, that's beautiful. Not beautiful
Beautiful hi
Damn cat Jesus Christ
That cat is loud as a man. Yeah. Yeah, he's jealous of the alien cat
I just got a banana coffee. It's a coffee place and so you know
I'm like you say banana coffee. Yeah, it's banana coffee. It's like banana cream a cold banana cream coffee. It's like so
Well, it's got like whipped cream on the top that's all sweet and then it's like inside
It's like hot. It's like the bitter coffee taste, but then like the sweet banana with it. It's really good
Yeah
It is really good, and then I got a salted caramel kind of one two
Yeah, so I got a couple coffee and I can't as page away this page up here
She was on earlier she was on
On live it seems you're on my burly. I don't know if she's still on anybody. No, I
Did see you know there are some people on right now. Okay, so this is
And what I have a question like you what do you mean by sponsoring like how late you're gonna go people keep sponsoring it
Um, of course, it'll just be like, you know, it's okay. It'll be like a couple of night because it won't be like, you know
If they continue if they get on time, I'll put it the next day, you know, or whenever they want me to do it, you know
and so
Or yeah, whenever like, you know, I'm doing paneling and then it's a closed panel and then they can go. Hey, you know
And so I think I think it'll be a good method. It's pretty
Pretty straightforward, but let the guy
Restart I just restarted just because I have to be careful sometimes with like
You're protecting your channel and no one chucking. Yeah, so
All good. Okay. Good. My tablet's
Charging up. I have a couple cords on the way too
Yeah, I'm getting a lot of stuff. I really needed like, you know
God he said 30 dollars to ban me. Yeah, he's gonna. Yeah, I think you're thinking nobody out
Yeah, I have to be careful who I bring up sometimes your band whose bands let me see. Oh, no, he's not buying
Am I ban? Oh, no, no, no, you're not
Good see how that goes for you brother
You know, it's like, it's really hard for me to say goodbye to anyone, because I just
love people.
I feel bad if I have to kick people off the show sometimes, but I got a, oh, look at,
when was this?
I have this old episode is running, and it's like pages and that's like, cute, it's kind
of different.
Ghost, I'm here. Ghost, are you there?
It's Paige. Ghost.
That was a really bad page.
Yeah guys, like people are like people are like, oh, you know
The internet is not you know, you can't make it to the panels not or you know running shows is not a job
And like it's not it's like guys. I'm trying not only trying for myself
I want you guys to like say hey, you know, you can have ideas and try things and no different
It's a new
Think the Wild West a little bit worse like there's not all these all these rules saying you can't do all these things
Kind of push the envelope a little bit, you know, sometimes the culture catches up with you, you know, but um the pad say that retire
Yeah, I think did it several years. Do you remember when Pat say Jackie's is the most racist joke in the world?
This movie called
Or it might have been Chuck Wowery, yeah, I think it was Chuck Wowery and Chuck Wowery made the racist joke
How to say Jack
Mervanna white
Okay, how's everyone doing? We're having a nice night
Chillin chillin I got a few decks. I got some copies. Oh, I've looked at this right now. I can't see anything
Now I see.
What's up, guys?
Those are good.
Okay, now I can put this in here.
Let me do a collective with the cat deck, okay?
So here's this cat deck, it's really cute, it says.
It says pause tarot, and it says future in your pause.
Okay, so this is the Paws Tarot.
It's really cute.
Super cute.
It's a very brighter weight-ish, but with cat themes.
They're like, they look like, they look like,
they ever see the cat like, I can has cheese,
or what is it called, Pushkin?
So I can has, no, that's not the I can has cheese
or the cat has the pushkin or something.
Ooh, it smells really good.
You're about to raise a $25 piece for a site,
uh oh, my ghost bounce, uh oh.
Oh well, maybe he'd be at me.
I think he didn't want to be balanced after he donated.
So it's a, no, there'll be others, but okay, what do we want?
Don't hang up on me spanky. Hey, okay, so here's for the check it
So this is for the this is a collective for the chest with the cat that okay
So first we have seven of one's okay seven of one so you're in guard you're in some or maybe we're all on guard
Maybe it's like a little bit we have to watch for me to defend some sometimes because sometimes we can be too defensive and
Then people that are actually trying to help we kind of push them away too sometimes right we can
But you know, you got maybe you got some people, you know
So imagine those are pitchforks and you know, sometimes we get in those situations where like we just have to defend ourselves, you know
and so
Maybe that's something in the past you've got to defend yourself, but you know, it's not like the worst
There's like nine of wands is really about like a lot of trauma. Okay, but look there's a tower happening
You know aren't these towers happening for everybody? You know, there's a little
little
Shocking like little disasters or little sudden changes and they're they go only you're going up. It's how we need the poo and
You know, there they go, but you know what cats always land on their feet. That's the thing about cats, right?
So we have to take that thing from the cat and just land on our feet and
Keep going, okay? So there might be something going on right now though. Oh look when we use our intuition about this
there's a cat high priestess
High priestess is all about having this we have our inner knowing intuition sometimes we need to go into meditation
silence and
and we know more than we think we do too, okay?
Let me see.
Advice for the chat.
Oh, okay, three of cups.
And it means enjoy things, enjoy life, celebrate.
Like we're having some drinks.
Cats are all getting drunk.
There should be lines of catnip.
They're just off the car
because that's not really appropriate
to show on the cat's car.
But yeah, they're doing some lines of catnip
and just drinking and...
You ever see the South Park
where like all the cats come over
and they start doing lines of coke
and like looking in Carmen's house
Yeah, okay
The panel is open that you are all welcome up. I will put the link again. You did there you go. Okay. Here you go
I'm gonna put a banner up thinking
Jamie until for another no a little after 10 30
Those link again, okay
Let's see another let me see what's so what's what's what's being hidden from us right now?
What are we saying? What's the little message we aren't seeing what's being hidden? Okay? Oh judgment
Maybe there's a judgment being called right now. We're not seeing it's being hidden
Maybe there's a it's like is this happening?
There's a trumpet being blown. It's a good thing about the trumpet is like that means kind of like oh test is over
Stop stop ever put down your pens time to time. It's and people are gonna
You know grade the test
So there we go.
There's like a little family down there saying,
hi, angel.
The angel cat, blowing the beautiful horn.
The cat looks a little bit cross-eyed, but okay.
What should we be focused on right now?
Ooh, moving on from something,
like going to calmer waters.
Maybe like, you know,
maybe getting away from our regular environment.
Going somewhere else, but
Basically changing our thoughts to to more calm thoughts you can see I usually on this card
There's like rough water on the one side and calm waters ahead, but this doesn't show like that and who else so what should we ask okay?
Who should we be on the lookout for
Ooh, the King of Swords, you're looking at me?
Okay, so I'm going to look out for some kind of Gemini, Aquarius, or Libra, which are the
air signs.
There's a lot about justice, a lot about communication intelligence, so you might, there's a person
like that you might want to be having a chat with, and if he has a little dog, he has a
little dog.
Cat has a, what is that?
Is that a dog?
They're really cute cards. Oh, how cute look at the back of them, too. They're so adorable
Yeah, watch. Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, it's gonna be Aquarius Gemini Aquarius. The Aquarius are
I'm an Aquarius moon Aquarius are very like they're like nothing. They're like
Like this
Hold on. Oh
They're like this Aquarius are they're like the third the gray alien, but they mean so they do love the cats, right?
They love cats
Here we go
There we go
See how cool yeah, so that's that's like an Aquarius they're like
They have a heart for cats. Okay. They like cats
Otherwise
They're kind of very very cool. Here's blue ghost. Okay, here we go. Hello
Ghostie, what's up? Hi, are you okay? It's a little bit upset in the chat
Yeah, they won't be nice to you in the chat I seemed upset are you you're not are you
Okay, this panther panel. Thank you. Jamie's cat was responsible in the panel until 10 30 p.m. Pacific Standard Time
I need to fix that PM twice. Okay
No
And there we go. Okay, so
Yeah, why do you think I'm a set though?
No, I don't think you're probably just like you're kind of like fighting this people were kind of like fighting the chat
But I was just kid. I was kind of kidding. There we go. There's
Join they can come up here and fight it
What's wrong guys, Joe's wants to fight he's looking he's looking for a fight. He's not he doesn't run from them
He looks for them
Here we go, because you're just my game
Because you can choose the color of the text. What color what color should this box be or your box of the what do you think?
Well, I'd say red brother. Okay. Yeah
Red
Let's run that bitch
That's it
There's red for you. Yeah, you're running a good panel
Yeah, I'll put red behind us too. Let me see like
Well background that would be
This is the closest I can get to red I think if it's in the back
No blue in the back. Yeah
Okay, yeah, how about the clouds you like the clouds?
This I love the clouds brother
There you go
Here we go whoo ghost we're going together in the clouds. This is romantic
Hello, come on girl. I know I mean not romantic in the romantic like you know, come on dude
Well, no romantic like not like you know been here since the beginning and you said that it's not the beginning
What if I always said you said maybe someday?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I made a comment.
You look good.
Don't take advantage of it.
Literally a match made in heaven.
Do you see how these two balls floating through the sky?
We're literally a match made in heaven.
We're in the heavens.
You want to hold hands and go up in heaven and debate everybody?
Let's fucking run it.
Let's run it.
Stop being weird, bro.
Stop asking me that shit.
I said look good.
It was a joke about it. I know it was but stop being weird the women just look at the women. We're straight. We're straight
You're not but this time this guy's definitely not straight you heard he's from New York, you know
Go ahead sir
Are you don't like a retard sir? You're gonna turn me into stone once I look at you. Oh, you don't know the fuck you're talking about
You're talking to ghost make make a question
Ask your friends if they have a very curious LES and make this one a laugh at each other
All right, cool, what do you want to say to go so I'm good. Oh, they see me screwing that ghost
They got good and scream. What do you want? What do you want to hear?
Why are you so angry today, bro?
What do you want why are you talking to me boy? Why are you so angry? Why you can't be happy?
I'm not angry. Well the burden of proof will be on you. I'm not
Psychic do I sound angry? Yeah, you sound like you're screaming at me right now.
You're so mad at me bro. Why are you cursing at me bro?
I don't give a fuck if I'm usually like that. I'm not like that. No, I'm not.
So what's your argument? You need a big hug?
Yes, he does
I don't need money I'm here chilling. What's the argument?
You don't have an argument fuck off. I know
Simple I ain't trying to hug you fuck off. I want to argue with you, bro
I'm gonna give you a nice then be gone. You thought you thought you thought you gonna be I put you on a shirt
Be very careful. I'll put you on a shirt. Yeah, I'm gonna give you the teddy bear hug
I will put you on a shirt, check the score, check the score, check the score, check the
score, fuck your head, check the score, you're, hug Saki, you're, check the score, check
the score, boy, I'm up, I'm up, I'm up, that means shut your mouth, ghost.
Do you know what check the score means?
Check the score
Check the score. Check the score. I already check I already checked it and the ghost
Oh ghost always wins. Ghost always wins brother ghost number one. We'll see you next time, bitch
Talk it now. I'll see you next time if you're not gonna talk it and shut the fuck up
They heard I'm up
Ghost, uh, yeah, you heard ghost always wins in which I do is win
Yeah, I won this one anything else. I already won
Check the score check the score
Check the score. I'll put you on a shirt. Don't talk about that. Check the score. Check the score
I'm not arguing. It's not you're not worth arguing with check the scores. I win
No, I'm not gonna shut my mouth. It's my panel. Don't fuck I paid for it. Oh my night. Did you pay for it?
Did you pay for this panel? You have to be happy then shut the fuck up dumb dumb the fuck up dumb dumb
All right, then talk some sense go ahead
Yeah, go ahead go ahead
You don't have to fuck your body
Yeah, it's not talking to me you're talking to me
I'll check the score which I win again. I will check the score. That's like that's like 9 to 2. That's like 9 to 2.
Yeah, I won 9 and you guys won 2. I'll put you on a shirt. Stop talking about that boy.
9 to 2. I'm often going to be smoking on you tomorrow. Ah, smoke on you tomorrow.
Listen, you got to pay at least $10
Yeah, I'm gonna be smoking on you tomorrow. I need at least
No, I already smoked already smoked your whole pack
I already smoked on all that okay, okay, ninja
So you don't have to fuck you're talking about no, I didn't be quiet
I'll put you in a shirt be quiet brother. You're a ghost. You're a ghost. I'm tired of smoking on y'all
I'm tired of smoking on y'all. I'm tired of smoking a check the score. I'm tired of smoking on y'all
I'm talking this ice. I am
So I key do you want you don't want to talk to me you're fine. I'm just
Quick if you don't mind I'm gonna put them on a shirt check the score. It's like nine to two
Look at your ghost emoji. Yeah, you better you get you better change it. I'll fucking smoke anybody
Okay, I'm gonna try a new let me see it. Let's run that bitch
Fuck it bring him back. Yeah, let him talk. So I keep on talk. Let him talk
Like you my sponsor in this yeah, I didn't take it. Oh, I didn't take it. Oh, I saw I'm so I let him talk. Yeah, let me talk
I'm gonna burn you up. Go ahead
I'm just adding the
I'm putting the link again guys again. Hold on one second. Oh, okay. No, I hope it's I hope it's open
It's open. I'm putting the link in again
Yeah, so what do you say check the score by the way?
But if you want something new what are you talking about?
Got the link got the link. Okay, I put pinning it. Okay, there's a link pinned. Oh, yeah, let's run it. Yeah, open me
Obviously obviously open panel with me. Let's run it
No
Yeah, Katie
Awakens with the s some psys ch e a w a k e n s
There we go, thank you so much why you quiet now check the score you want ten
Let's run it I already checked it double checked it check to the third time
Go ahead
You're too fucking stupid to have the conversation
Yo, smoke a blaster.
I'm giving my-
You're...
You're on no piece of ghost.
Ghost always wins.
You haven't realized that by now?
Alright, go ahead.
I'm giving you the chance.
Go ahead.
I am- I am a good ghost.
What you fucking hide at the conversation are you just you fuck now what you are you two fucking stupid?
Let's run that bitch dog
I
Tell you I want everything I want it all
I want everything
I want everything I want it all
Let's run that bitch dog
Money
Too stupid to even run it psyche. I apologize. I know I donated money your channel. That's your money psyche
You do whatever the fuck you want to do with it
Thank you. Don't keep these retards up there. They're too stupid to have the conversation, sir
You don't have a station you dumb. Well, let's run it. Fuck it. I'm down. I'm down for a little I'm down for a little
Well the burden of proof beyond you are gonna go there. Let's run
That's all you know because you don't know how to have argument look up to me, sir
You're saying dumb dumb because why are you why are you saying the burden of proof?
Why are you saying dumb dumb because of me?
That's why you're saying it because you don't know how
No, the only yeah, you heard the only reason you say that because of me because of ghost because of ghost
Get my dick get my dick out of your mouth, sir
So I keep I don't want to be
Are you having a party and listen to my show at the party or what's going on?
Yeah, you don't know yeah, I'll take both of you both are fucking retard I'll take both of you
My dick is in your mouth. It sounds cute. Are they cute? I
Don't know psyche when you game
I'm asking I'm asking LES. Oh, they got they got quiet for a second. Oh my gosh. Wow
It's okay never mind never mind
They might be cute psyche, but they're fucking retarded sir yo shut up ghost
No, I'm gonna handle this conversation because check the score
Ghost always wins go ahead. I always win brother. Why you wanna argue with me?
I didn't challenge you. You know goofball. Did I challenge you sir? Okay goofball
Okay, good. Did I challenge you?
All right, then shut the fuck up in yeah ghost always win. Ghost always wins
No
Shut the fuck up
Check the score
You say one more thing
I'm gonna put you on a t-shirt
Say one more thing
You're on a t-shirt
You're gonna keep talking
Check the score
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about
Sir
Big ghost in here
You know what the fuck you're talking about, sir?
What now, psyche? Hey, psyche, real quick.
Let him go. Let him talk to that stupid.
I know you're trying to...
I know he's retarded.
Come on now. Let's have it.
Yeah, let's run it.
Let's run it.
I think the rooster is more smarter than you, sir. That's my claim
Make the claim
Elias loves to eat cock like that's what he's saying
Why do you see I do too, okay, but you're gonna make the thing that goes like the cock go ahead the bird
How do I like to eat cock? Go ahead.
Yo, yo, you're a ghost. You like to eat the cock from ghosts?
You're saying that you don't know what stuff you're talking about.
You keep talking about it and putting it on a t-shirt, yeah?
Are you cool about it? Are you cool about it?
Are the guys from the school of Athens? Is that school of Athens?
Yeah, that shit is funny, bro.
He's too stupid to have that conversation.
All you retards is too stupid to have it.
Yo, you retards, bro. Shut up.
Gordon, if he was on you, what are you talking about?
Yo, go ahead and eat the rooster.
How many times do I have to say let's run it?
Check the score!
Yo, shut the fuck up!
Well, never mind.
I'm gonna talk, if not, prove me wrong.
I am gonna talk to you.
Alright, here's the sucker.
So you're gonna leave if you're gonna reach
You don't cry like a little baby you don't you don't the fuck you're talking about sir
You have no idea what you're talking about explain. What do you know? What are you doing right now?
Explain go ahead
Explain what are you doing now?
Talking to your dumbass
Guaranteed you're not gonna explain it. What do you do? Yeah, what else are you doing? What else are you doing?
What else are you doing? You don't know you fucking stupid answer
Yes, Paige, can you come up here like I think ghost needs to be wrangled in
Oh
What do you mean by ghost needs to be wringled in yo God I need to come up God come up
Well fuck God he fucked you you both don't know the fuck you're talking about
Straight up you have no idea. No, that's not your herd. You don't know what the fuck you're talking about sir
Never to much how to challenge you you're still
Conversation
Yeah, okay. Cool. That's a good argument. That's not a good argument
Like I agreed
Person bro, I don't even know what that means. Go ahead and explain that. You know what?
What's up? I don't know which I paid for this
Yo, you want to go to the hell fire?
Yes, my cousin goes
You're too stupid to have the conversation I might answer no you die or you won fucking retard. I already burnt your ass up three times
I'm not answering the question you won't want you won't walk to the door. I'm done. Oh, you want to you want to walk to the hell
What's up? I'll take you to hell with me sir. You're too stupid to win the conversation
So I'm gonna talk to you sir your ghost you won't get burnt. Come on. You'll be fine. How am I gonna be burnt?
You're not gonna get burnt bro
I'll take you the hell man. You got your ass whooped. Yeah, officer. I'm the devil. You got your ass whooped, sir
You got your ass whooped
No, it's not your hurt. You got your ass whooped boy. I'll go check the score and then you say you're
You're one of this. You don't want none of this. I don't want none of this already won already won
You're hurt I'll take you the hell and I bring you back
Yeah, I already won. I already won
Would I like another piece sure
Well, you have to admit you have to you have to admit that I won the round like that rooster do so, huh?
Would you like a part to you at least admit what I want a party? Oh, you want powerful? Okay? Let's run that big star
Hi coffee. No you lose you lose every one of them. I don't want to part you dumb dumb
You lost
Now you're a pervert, but by the way you lost
And I just want you to know that goes to that you goes
You're a fruitcake.
You like to eat roosters, you hear?
That's ghost, you hear?
Go see ghosts you're not talking no more
The rooster got your tongue. Did I not just say that I was done talking. Shut your mouth. You stupid to have the conversation
Yo, you suck on the rooster. That's why he's still quiet. Yeah
No, I'm just smarter than all of you. I'm better than all of you
We still boy
My burden will prove to be on you. How am I risk the board go ahead if you stupid that the conversation?
That's why I'm done talking
Talking okay, you're too stupid to have the conversation. Okay, fuck boy
Okay, go ahead and make the argument. I said saying okay make your argument. You're gonna fuck
That's a good argument. Shut the fuck up. That's a good argument. Come fuck. Yeah, exactly. So stop talking to me
I'll burn your ass up boy.
I'll burn your ass up.
I thought so.
Next.
You're fucking retarded.
You fucking retarded.
How am I retarded sir go ahead?
How am I retarded go ahead how I'm retarded go ahead
So you don't know what the fuck you're talking about sir. You know I'm talking fuck it up
So why would you make it? Why would you make it clean when you don't know what you're talking about?
man shut the fuck up
Is this a real fight?
Shut the fuck up my dude. Shut the fuck up. You dirty ass boy
dirty ass pull a card
No, it's not a real fight at all. No, it's not a real fight. You just joking around
Okay
Man will be men
What are you doing?
We definitely don't want a card though, babe. Fuck all that I didn't ask if you wanted a card
All right, that's fair enough. Yeah, I know you didn't
Watch out watch out. He hate women's you better watch out. Oh
Pitch yeah, yeah, I hate women. I forgot about that. I hate women
Well, I should hit you too, sir. If you're you're the biggest bitch. I know
For them you're the biggest bitch. I know you like to suck on the rooster you're her
I ain't I ain't suck it on nothing you're
Sucking on a little bit of logic
Make their argument. Let's run. Let's run it. Let's go
You're from it. If you would like to leave I would love to hang out page
I ain't suck it on nothing dumb dumb. You suck in the rooster cop
Burn the proof is only what am I sucking on sir?
No, it doesn't make I ain't sucking on nothing
Well, I'm letting the retard talk to me. I mean let the retard be a retard
Well, let me talk
How do you know sir, you're gonna make the argument. I'm not how do you know my gender sir?
Good how I
Would actually help you with your argument because I mean actually you kind of make sense you know what the fuck you were talking about
And I would actually help you
Stop being mad be happy
Happy about what what am I gonna be happy about?
You have to be happy. You don't know the fuck you're talking about and actually tomorrow if you if you send me if you send me a message
Sir, you say help me and you say daddy you help me daddy
Help me daddy
We're talking about just helping you
I asked the page page. Are you here? Yeah, I just don't know where to put myself in. Yeah, my answer you sorry
Not much just listening to y'all. What are you doing?
Doing good being men
arguing
Clearly, I don't want I don't want to argue what you bro. You just being done right now
You can't argue I win ghost always
You're not gonna win
All right, I won shut up. All right be quiet. It's fine. It's all right fair enough
Page what do you have to say about what I asked I asked for you. I don't know. I just asked for you I guess
Just trying to give you a good vibe. I don't know
Yeah, yeah, by the way page. I didn't ask for reading. I just asked for you to be good
No, I know and I'm here and I'm not doing a reading so
Yeah, yeah
I am ridiculous you always page. You always give a reading
It's either request that's fair. It's either requested or I'm here with psych or I'm on my own live which is about
All right
Hypothetically, let's say like every time that you join
Hypothetically people ask you for a reason therefore you do do a reading more than not. Yes
Well, yeah, but but hypothetically I like you being here
I don't like to read what you you guys are. No, I don't like it
I asked for you to be here just to be here and hang out
And look
No reading. I'm just hanging out. Did you just drop the cards like a badass?
I feel like drink down though
All right, his cards here, which is my area where I do them
There's people here that love your reading page. I'm not that person, but I want I want you to be here
I don't not like I don't know. It's fine. We're good. I know there's no cards. Look at hands
hands up. I
Can't see a show it again
Put them up. No higher. No, I'm up. No, that's arm for hair
Put them up
No
This thing put them up
I don't trust her psyche kicker kicker. I don't trust her. No, I ain't trusting that bit
All right, I ain't trust from her though
You sound like a robot. What? You're doing it again ghost
I'm doing what again sir
You're hating on women again. I
Can't know no one
Come on. I didn't say it. I didn't say it. I said hate
Who am I hating on go ahead? Yeah, how many women are up here?
It's a way of cycle for my cars. You just same as page. I tell them both the same thing
I carry on go. How am I hating? Yeah, I'm gonna carry on God
Boy, you don't fuck you're talking about you don't fuck you're talking about you're too stupid to have the conversation
You paid for this panel go ahead
I want you up here. I paid for it. So I want you up here. Please come up. I'm here. I'm here
I'm just what the fuck you thought you don't know fuck
Now I want a little piece of you sir, you don't fuck you're talking about
If you're not too stupid
Didn't know what you're talking about. What what the fuck were you even talking about go ahead?
What are you saying kid?
Why are you so upset with everybody
Seven a bad week. Well, I'm upset with the retard. They don't know what the fuck they're talking about
At all did I just did I not got did I not just prove that?
I asked, I asked him, come back up here.
I even said I paid for it.
Please come back up, explain what you were saying.
You don't have to fuck your talking about, sir.
Ghost always wins.
I gave you three strikes, you struck out.
Yeah, I gave you three strikes, sir,
and then I paid your back up here because of you.
You paid, we restarted, here we are, okay.
You wanna strike out again?
Yeah, and you still don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
I ain't gonna strike out, trust that.
you even told me I lost and you
You lose you said you lose you spelled it L. What did I lose?
Okay, I said that to you the burden of proof would be on you, but you said I would be on you
You fucking have that conversation, but I lose when did I say that sir? What country are you from?
No, the you said I just said that no you know when you win that I one time did I say that what that means?
I lose all right be gone. You don't the fuck you're retarded
You spell loose. You're trying to be funny. You're not
You are but you're not sir. I'm not trying to be funny. There's no trying to be a third
I'm talking the page if you don't mind. Oh, I'm sorry. Go ahead. Yeah
And thank you. I'm talking to the second page if you don't mind sir
Fucking retard
You are retarded sir
All right, I did start it and I'll finish it. Let's run that based on
you
I didn't I did I lost it. I'm talking the page. I won
Yeah, let's run it. I'll give you 60 seconds. Let's run it
Let's run it. You want to run it? Let's run it
Let's run it. Let's run that bitch dog. You cock sucker
Let's run it
Go eat a cup. I'm not not answering you. I'm saying I'm answering you. What's your warm that mother?
Yeah, let's run it dumb ass, dude
I'm trying to talk to page you guys
Smarter he more looser
Don't want to talk to me actually yeah, I know I apologize
Because you're being a jerk a little bit
Well, I'm debating these people not you
Well, what the fuck?
Wait, this is all right now you are keep talking. Let's run that bitch. Let's run it like you. Can you let vanguard up?
Please I want him to debate ghosts. Yeah, I'd let vanguard up. I paid for it. Let him up
If you guys don't mind
page
No, can you guess my
See here hold on hurt my hearing. Oh, I thought I saw him backstage. Oh, I don't see him
So they're gonna step up to me
That's fucking run it
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
that
is going to run it or not
now it's not going to happen
What do you mean by that?
He doesn't want to retouch up on the panel at the same time. I understand sir. You don't the fuck you're talking about
I actually pay for this and I I asked for a page not you
And what and what you paid for what and what you shouldn't be here?
You're stupid to have the country doesn't work that way pal
What do you want to pay started paid you want to use the argument?
You just
I sponsored it and you shouldn't be here, sir.
No, no, everybody can come up.
It doesn't work like that.
You can only sponsor the family.
You know me.
You know girls, please, an open family.
Everybody can be here.
I'm trying to talk to Paige if you don't mind.
Well, do we have anything of intelligence or purpose
to talk about, or what?
Are we going to talk about it?
No.
No
With all due respect boys, that was what we do in here. Let's discuss purpose in life. What is purpose?
Not this what we're doing right now probably. This is exactly not purpose. Yeah, okay. Thanks, but it's fun. None the less
This pathing throws me off. I didn't even know you're up your side. This this eye with the pat name. It threw me off
I didn't know what I kind of did to you actually, but I thought I was so stoned you have an excuse
No, that's right. I don't get stoned. No, cuz you're good. It's a natural high
It's a lie. Hi. It's high on life. We made them leave page poor guy
guess that was money well spent huh thank you ghost and then there were four
so your days going well but you're much better now or you're still having a
rough day um well no I'm like it is what it is you have to get over it can't
change it right it's gonna happen every year so but yeah I'm alright and doing
reading actually that really like made me feel better so I always like help
Yeah, that was great man. Thanks again. Yeah, you're welcome. Thanks for coming
Now I'm just tired
No, I don't mind the long readings I just you know me I just don't like taking up people's time too much
Oh, fuck. That's what I'm on there for it's like the one thing I do
We should play trivia one of these nights guys like I kind of miss doing that with everybody. Oh
It's been a while. It's I think so hasn't it? What was the last time we played?
it's been about a week for me well that's too long isn't it yeah at least once a day
at least once a day sometimes twice keep it fucking real right
like how much random shit do you guys know like people bring it up and like you just
i know so many things like it's almost random shit but it's from trivia you guys have to be the same
Like, every time you hear something in public or someone asks a question, you're like,
I know that fucking weird little answer, because we play trivia.
It's making us... keeping us smart, either.
Some people know everything.
You ever know if there's one person that knows everything?
Yeah.
Like, wow, man.
This is amazing.
Everything is that they're... bring something to the table, don't they?
It's good as a collective, though, yeah.
Yeah.
If you've got five or six people in there, they all pretty much get everything.
You know what the best part is is people don't fight because their brains are busy thinking of answers instead
Definitely curves the fighting
Just tempers it a little bit, you know and the dummies. I don't want to participate. They just fucking they just leave and come back
Yeah later on to fight
Oh, I guess I could I mean, I don't know what's up to psych
I'm exhausted
Whatever
What
You like we have it over the panel
Banger wants to come say hi to Godie, I think
It's too late not for me. It was for ghosts. Hello
Hello, it's random guy. Hey, where am I?
Thank you. What up, man? Oh shit. What's up? What's going on wrong place, huh?
Fuck yeah, wrong panel. I'm sorry, man. Oh shit. What's going on? Vanguard here Vanguard here. Who the fuck's that?
Yeah, I'm still waiting to talk like oh tea in prairie on you and what's who's this new person?
Are you gonna be nice thank God
It depends if you like nice or copa static copa static, it's okay. I like copa static
Well
Go ahead
What what I've just come here
You know what he wants to talk about go ahead talk about what you won't really want to talk about we all know what it is
Go ahead. Go ahead. It's an American panel. Let's talk about American stuff. Yeah. Yeah, go ahead. Go ahead
Canadian but whatever
by proxy
I'm kind of I kind of feel American now see
You're on the border, right? You're basically on the border.
No, I'm kind of like in the middle of the border.
Canada's on the border though.
Oh yeah, of course. I thought you meant like province-wise.
You're like a cousin.
Yeah, that's right.
A cousin you don't want to fuck with, oh dear.
Are you mad about the tariffs vanguard is that what it is what tariffs don't affect me directly it only affects use guns
Well, they're gonna affect you they're gonna affect you directly
No, they're not gonna affect us. Oh
American consumer
Well, you're in the UK, so we made a deal with the UK separately from the EU, so...
No, there's been no deal made with the UK.
Yes, yes, Stammer made a deal. He made a backdoor deal with Trump.
No, there's been no deal.
Stammer was just in Trump's ass, don't worry.
If you look at it, Donald Trump dropped the papers
and Keir Stammer picked up the empty pieces of paper
and put them back in his filaments.
nice little boy yeah with a nice little note in there saying whatever you want donald's
fuck off come on
anyway goatee can we have a decent conversation for once
go ahead i'm waiting how is your non-existent feat doing
i've been dreaming of them every day ever since i lost them
Yeah, what's that? What are you doing for me to get them?
Um, I don't invest in you it's dollar. It does that help
No
Your heart you really are a heartless person
Yeah
Yeah, he doesn't give a shit
well
Some people just don't
I know I'm never going to wipe these bum. I'm never going to exchanging cost to me back and I can't afford to charge
these fucking wheelchair up but goatee knows I don't disrespect him.
Not at all.
Yeah, okay, what do you look like?
What do I look like I look like Donald Trump on steroids?
Let's see
I look like Donald Trump on steroids prairie
Well, if you're not gonna come up and you're gonna make fun of somebody like that, then maybe you shouldn't right?
You know, honestly, I think I've seen you vanguard and I can't diss you. You look like a normal person
Yeah, man go T knows actually go T knows me. I've known go one time
I don't know what happened to you, but you stopped coming up for somebody somebody said something to you or something
But you look normal
There's nothing I could really say
What is normal these are your brain your brain is fucked up absolutely fucked
But you looked almost like a decent human being I mean, I am a decent human being
Yes, I got your ass. You're decent my ass. There's nothing decent about you fuck face
Fuck you
Well
What happened to you? What happened to you? Did you gain like four pounds?
No, I start
Anyway, go to eat how you don't fella and I'm doing fantastic feet and all I'm doing fantastic
Yeah, you want a picture of my feet? I'll take a picture right now. You want to see them they look great
It's I don't beat it. I don't need to see that
For everyone to see fucking my beautiful feet except for the big one big toe is still healing from the fall I had last year
But other than that, it looks pretty good
Careful people are gonna try to sell them. I don't care. I don't care
Profits hold on let me take this picture hold on that'd be a hustler
I'm just kidding. That's fucked up
By the way
All right
Wow
Fucking clouds in the background who farted. Oh, it's my phone vibrated on the desk. Oh your phone
No
We go
All right, here they come you ready?
Yeah, okay these bad boys remember I had an accident my big toe last year, so don't judge
Everyone's gonna do right well let them fuck them. Yeah, let's see easy. You ready you can post this on your fucking channel and then you can lick it
looks like it's just a foot. Zoom in. The big toe is like a little black at the top.
Look at him zooming in.
All right Paige, your turn.
Fuckin show your feet. That's what we're doing. We're all gonna do it. It's okay. We're all gonna do it
Just asking for it y'all
Someone gonna make five bucks off of those. Enjoy it. Sebastian enjoy it. I know you
love those enjoy it. Well, they couldn't call you a black foot kinda goatee. Not me. Why
you got a problem with black feet? No, they couldn't call you a black foot. We actually
Well
Don't be disrespectful
Are you saying I don't know Indian native history goatee? I wouldn't say nothing of the sort lad
nothing
You know everything
Yes, indeed
You try to tell us every day
Yes, oh
Sebastian you only want to see women's feet
Yeah, good luck
Cuz no woman's gonna come over there to show you her feet
Why'd you go away, let's let's get something cleared up why did you vanguard and use the bash and come over here
Why did you guys come over here? Why'd you follow me over here?
First of all don't be paranoid. I don't know no no no no no no no no for real. Why'd you follow me here? I
Didn't follow you anyway. Of course you fucking followed me here. You never came here before
Fuck off, of course I've been here before.
Fuck you, you dead, you fucking liar man.
I've been here for almost two months.
Have you never been here before?
I've even disrespected you here.
I've talked to people.
Yeah, because you followed me over here, that's why.
And I've talked to Prairie on his own page before.
Oh, you talked to Prairie, have you?
Yeah, because you followed me here,
that's the only reason you know these people.
He's embarrassed now. Yeah, you got sick of Jay
Because you've talked bullshit again goatee, let me explain to everybody
Vanguard's been kicked off more panels than I have you know why because he's fucking boring
That's why this panel is dying right now because he's up here
The only reason this whole fucking thing is floundering
So why are you here vanguard to kill another fucking panel? Is that it?
Of course psyche doesn't deserve this good thing goes paid for this fucking panel
Page tears into another direction, please. Yeah, I've been trying for a bit
Fucking bang god dude. He's like a cancer
Well, like
You've got black feet and you talking about cancer
See, I can't win with you fucking people
One day I have no feet the next day I got cancer feet. What the fuck?
I can't come up. This is this is what would happen
That's enough
No more never again
Fairy page. Can you remember giving me a tarot reading the other day?
Yes, I remember that. You can remember that.
You make it sound like prairie and tarot.
You're singing it.
like I'm singing it.
Big body, big body.
Hey Christine.
You know, we had a lot of people follow us here
and they're trolls and they try to start shit every
flippin' day.
I just want you to know you're not the only one.
Oh, no, no, no, and I understand that I wanted to hear him say it. Yeah, and then
Prior to ghost paying for this panel Jamie paid for it to be opened up
Then it went to summer then me and then ghost so there should have been there's enough to go 12 hours
That have been paid and ghost told
psyche it doesn't have to be for the panel it could be for anything but of
course he needs to make it about him to be the winner
There you go. That's fine. That's fine. If he wants to be the winner in his own mind and
Psyche 30 40 bucks. That's fine
Psyche wins we're happy
And that's all the bottom line is yeah, and thank you ladies for also sponsoring the next 12 hours
This will be great. Thank you. It's the you know, so thank you prairie because I did
I did take I did take the heart and observed and took on board what you told me the other day
You or has it yet
Or come to fruition whatsoever
Well, the fruition is exactly what I said in what you told I'm already in every
information of the nations of
conversations
What do you just say?
Christie, thank you for paying. Thank you for paying
She didn't pay for you
Well, no, it's it's to get psyche a little bit of money that he needs and we keep a panel open
Nothing wrong with that. Yeah, absolutely not. It's cheap entertainment and you know, we enjoy one another
Nothing wrong with that at all. That's why I'm saying thank you for being
But I just want you to know, buddy, we all have those issues of these people following us. Trust me. It's like, oh my God.
And the ones that are coming here have really been starting problems.
You know what it's like, Christine? It's like stepping on dog shit on your way home and you track it into the house.
You can't track it.
What would you know about...
Get off my shoe, van guy.
What would you know about stepping on dog shit when you've got your feet losing?
The ones that have come here...
A great people we've got a lot of great people that have come here. Yes. We have a more more great people than not
Right you you're 100% correct I
Don't know thank you. Why why is the picture up and not us is there?
Then the send don't be doing anything stupid. We'll hunt you down
Random you know vanguard
No, but I hear him. He's always
Random guy what what state of murk is why Marcy
Two people with a thousand names
I am the Van Gogh, but anyway, anyway random guy
I'm great. I'm quite enamored with your hair. And now they're making videos Marcy
Quite enamored with your big
Who's making video? No one of the tolls and one of them might feel very threatened by she she is threatening me
I live in Florida, I live in a standard
Your Florida girl
Floor Raider Floor Raider
What a place did this dream was in memoriam of one crucible ghosts God rested soul. Thank you
The peace brother. Oh there he is
Is she are you intoxicated tonight or the women gonna be cussed out again again?
No, I I'll give you a
Pack real quick. I will cuss women out
that's ok but I will not send for them
don't worry we know you won't
don't worry well you'll need to pay that
if you're too retarded to make the statement then actually I'll crash out then fine
you'll be the last one to send
you think anybody's going to be
going to shake your tent real quick nobody gives a fuck you're a disgusting little
why do you have a problem with that they're boobs who care why do i have a problem with
you shaking your tits on the internet for money because why do i have a problem with you i
think you'd be ten dollars and you know suck a dick first of all first of all i first of all
So you try to do something you're talking about ma'am
I am glad you know what I do stupid that I have the conversation about sex book ma'am
All right, so I paid for this panel while you're here
You paid after Jamie that opened it up
Dum-dum oh sweetheart, I can show my cash
Would you like to yeah, go ahead and show I paid a lot more than you did. Oh, yeah
But not in general
I think
Society then women who do this on my panel
you. Why the fuck are you
here? I don't want you here.
You haven't paid $25 to have me
already paid it. You don't fuck
Oh, wait a minute. $25. I didn't
pay you. I'm because I have
paid for a string to be open.
So, I'm saying I paid. I paid
You can do whatever you want with that money. It's not
Okay, do you fucking stupid to realize I paid
Yeah, you're too drunk and stupid to realize what you at first
I mean
I'm not too drunk. I know you said how to roll
Not psyche come on now
I have one that my mother's
handed down to me.
I honestly would have to go get it
because it's a very expensive piece
of jewelry with my other weeks.
Um, no, it's 1 30 in the morning. I'm not waking up my family to get in the safe
I'll get it out tomorrow though
It's a very dainty woman's
Um, I don't think so
probably is. So, fuck I paid money for it. You got some dumb bitch. But it was it was passed out. Um,
my mom died 27 years ago and I got it when she passed. 27 year, but I'm so sorry. 27 years ago.
And then with their blue diamonds, I have their blue diamonds, too.
You got 27 years that changed your mind, but you're still a dumbass. Yes, I have their blue diamonds.
You think that would be set that would be considered a sapphire. No, no, they're not set fire
I don't think Rolex ever used blue diamond. The blue diamonds aren't blue diamonds aren't in my Rolex
I got a set of earrings and an extra sister blue diamonds because
We don't care about you blue time
I had people in and out of my house all the time so they
Man you're already I should have moved over for Jack on the fucking
We don't care
For me, I well I paid for this
cares
Right. Well, well, maybe you should pay. Maybe we'll care of it.
I paid for this. I paid for this.
I have. I don't, I don't throw in people's face.
I'm gonna pay. I'm gonna pay.
He pays. He's gone.
He pays too. Quite frequently.
I'll pay more than you.
That's who he tells the male.
I'll pay more than you, Gary.
I paid for this. I paid for this.
Hey, I paid for this.
If that's exactly what Christine does and that she paid for it.
I paid for this.
I
Shit for the last
He literally
Let's run that bitch
Yeah, he doesn't realize because he's not here when he's sober to see how we support psyche
Go ahead, what's your argument? How do you score him more than me?
Guys, I'm here. I'm here listening, but it goes and it goes. Yes. I very much
Since the beginning
Here we go again calling me names you happy
First of all, I did offer you, you know, the sponsor slot and you said, oh, yeah
What's with like throw it up at my face like well I gotta be more than one sponsor, but fuck it. I'll sponsor tonight
Let's learn that bitch no refunds bitch
Yeah, boot this motherfucker
That's why I give more. Hey, I'm smarter than all of you. That's why I give more money than one
Fucking dumb asses. Oh
My god
You gotta be a little bit more sick in the head. Come on now. Yes
I was hey, I was genius, you know, we always cover our own ass, you know what I'm saying
Is that a troll
I'm smarter than you brother
This is him
What's your argument?
You ain't gonna kick me
Let's go kick me, go ahead
I've been with my granddaughter all day
I haven't looked at any of my emails
Post them today
Last night
This is only until like 1030
That was Jamie's till 1030
And then summers
And then it should be mine
Ghost is over then
Well, ghost doesn't start.
you know what? Shut up. Shut up as you want with the the panel. You know that. My grand
daughter and my I mean, it goes to that one. It goes. It's like it doesn't like the sponsoring
the panel doesn't say you can you own the panel. You can do anything you want and blah
blah blah in the first place but it just says like when I was told I also like to kick
I would never say that I still do that bullshit. No, he never said 25 bucks, which I gave 30
Why Christine gone it's too late. It's too late
that's fine. I mean, I want
I did donate the money, but
but you didn't donate it at the time for
I did donate it. I did donate it.
you said you said you said this is not pretty said use it for whatever you want.
I did say that. Yes, I did. I did say that.
how much how much you make a day in donations
is this a
I'm just curious how much you make from this. Um, I'm just curious to be honest
25 Bugs
It depends on the day honestly and who's on
Some some days I don't make some days have been very quiet. That's why I need I do need to like
Survive and trying to upgrade a lot of my equipment. I want to get my computer fixed
I want to get some new equipment for the for filming and stuff. So I'm investing it right back into the show
You should have told him like in in America. It's kind of rude to ask how much people make
Yeah, man, don't do that here
Are you taking the piss most Americans
Most Americans all I ask that like how much do you make they're considered it's kind of fucking rude, dude
Yeah, we don't have those questions
Do it's not like asking me how much I have an egg with no
That's why he thought he was going to be scripting like yesterday
Yesterday, I looked at it. I'm just on this. Yeah
There's like huge super chat super chat
Whoa, hold on Arbiter
And put my glasses on I need my glasses for this
Don't forget
Forget Google takes like 20 fucking five or fifty
They take 30%
Guys, but then if you because because google or because you the youtube does
Proper from super chats too. I think it does help the algorithm and them promote if they know
I think it's just good in general if there's activity like super chats and
And other stuff it just makes your channel look better for them
And plus the ghost ain't doing it for psyches do it for himself. It's ego
My case
Just thanks for the support ghost
How do you, how do you guys, you like these glasses? Hold on. How do you like these?
Good work, Ghost.
I like the other ones.
Do you like that? Are these bomber glasses, Christina?
Yeah. Murderer.
Yeah, no, I don't like them as much as your other ones.
You look like they're pretty rough.
Yeah, okay.
I mean, dumb or not, I think your other ones look more appealing on you.
What is that bell thing?
I'm sorry. I didn't hear you.
Oh, no, that's okay.
Yes. I love your dead feet.
Where can I sponsor your new
Tesla feet? Oh, on my channel.
There's a there's a little cash
up button over there. You can
just go over there and you can
send whatever you want. We're
halfway to our goal. Are you
Well
I was looking at a Tesla to buy it because I want buy a new car, but then I decided I don't want
Well, my son bought the one I was looking at so I can't do that right out of the water ugly-ass car get a Jeep
Not a Jeep girl
Keeps it great
I'm still I'm still curious. What are the cyborg feet of Tesla type gonna work for you go to?
Well, they're gonna make me jump higher and run faster
Maybe like a South African running out the country
And you know
If you bend over I can plant it straight up your ass too. How about that?
Oh, Jamie, what's up girl?
I'm so baked right now. I can't talk. Oh, Cherokee's a nice. Yeah
It's kind of a ground charity. I have a Lexus girl kind of a Lexus car. Well, yeah, you have blue diamonds.
Well, no, they're given to me. Yeah.
The ground charity is even better than a Cherokee Jeep. I like the Wrangler so they're cool.
I still prefer... I still prefer Landro of us to be honest, yeah.
Well, okay, we all have our own thing, I mean...
No trucks, no we don't have trucks.
They said you're a Jeep girl, I'm just not a Jeep girl.
I'm not a Tesla boy either, remember?
I mean also kind of the SUV for me and the G makes sense where I live, right?
Right.
Also that too.
Where a luxury car makes sense where I live.
Practicality.
I quite like a Mercedes C-Class to be honest.
Once you get a job, maybe you can buy one.
Oh, that's awesome.
I have two Mercedes who says they don't have a Myback.
Go back your back is broken your back is broken your feet are fucking unexistent
He gets a big kick out of it you can tell carry on carry on van guy
At least me and you can have a laugh, Gorty, and that's for me.
His body is not nearly as bad as the couple of trolls that come in here after us, I'm seriously.
No, there's a difference between, but there's a difference between what your trolls do and what my trolls do.
My trolls they're more like pests and they they've killed a panel to board them with it
You know what it means you're your trolls are coming and scream and yell
This guy will come up there and go
For hours nobody can understand a fucking word he's saying
I kind of do but only because only because you know, I know a few other people from the UK and things like that that's how they talk
Thank you psych you guys am I fucking crazy or is your bells going like little jingle bells or something in the background?
Are those the fogs outside my house you're hearing
But they were on there I think when you weren't on panel
Yeah, they're crickets and frogs or whatever and they come out at night once the sun comes up. They go away. It's quiet again
Now somebody's playing bells
Right
I mean I'm sure a summer can
Let's all pray for the summer send good vibes for summer tomorrow
I didn't even know you were up here
I
Would you like to talk about
One it while we do the trivia and then Christian. Why are you talking to me shut the fuck up every time somebody gets an answer
I can play that bell. Oh my god, shut up
Okay, why should I shut up we need more sound effects here. What do you mean? There's not going on
the
Well, you don't know how to shuffle your cards girl
Well, I haven't seen you doing anything of the fucking sort. So till then don't judge me. I don't claim to do that dumb dumb
That's not my claim when he first came here
He says he didn't believe in it and didn't want cards now all of a sudden he's asking for cards make that make sense
I didn't ask you did I ask her did I ask her card?
Christine did I ask for a card?
I heard you earlier a fight for a card. Yeah, I'd rather give money. No, I did not ask the
I'd rather give money than to hear you talk.
And what kind of card is that by the way? Did you pull that?
What was it? The ghost card? Ghost gives money card?
Or do you not know what the fuck you're talking about? Why don't you do another super chat?
the
would you put it would you put a jet point Jupiter is a planet and jet I don't
know what the fuck jet is but you would a jet Jupiter is a planet man your
point is
If you're too fucking stupid to have the conversation, you shouldn't have it. Oh, I really don't want to have the conversation with you
So I'll accept it. Let's run that bitch dog. I'm stupid. No, you're not gonna accept it. Let's run it. Let's run it
Are you running away? You scared you run away? Yeah, absolutely
You if you're on the way you lose absolutely
You're running you lose
so how much money do I have to send to get this bitch off of you, I've sent plenty of money, how much money I got to send, it's like
by the way, if you run, you lose, just like, no
I accept losing, it's okay
there's always the money, I'll win anyway
if you continue then alright, I'll let it go, I'll let it go
close, one million dollars then
for Christine
I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say that I'm not going to say
There are you there
Smash are you there?
He always has problems with his Mike smash and unmute yourself honey, Christine
You know what the problem is they heard you and they watch one if you would shut up
Is that is that smash? Yes
Thanks
You just have to talk over him smash
Or pay more than me
Oh my god, look at you tonight
What the most bizarre scary pictures
What's this? Oh, look at this scary
You can sponsor as many as you want sweetheart
You sound like I'm gonna get you you sound like over like you're freaking me out. I'll be honest with you
What I'm gonna get you
You're weird
Yeah, it is weird. Yeah, that's all bitch. Why are you here?
I'll beat you. Here we go. There we go. Miss. I'm cookie monster next to other side of fozzie. Hold on. There we go
I want my ladies next up here actually, but I won't pay okay
Okay, so cookie monster can be next to the Joker and then I want to be part of the angels
You can be on the bottom. Oh, okay. So LES is left. Okay. So, so now I'm on top of I'm on
Do you want to be on top of me or be on top of you?
I just want to be part of the angels. I don't care where I'm at. Okay. You're part of the angels
Always wants to be included
You're joining I hit no more. I already joined it
But you can't use your ever I put guys. I put a ghost emoji in the in the emojis
It's like one of our ghosts, you know, Christine by the way, that's a moji from girls go ahead and use it Cristin
And by the way, every time you use it every time you use it pay a sci-fi books
For an M year
Hey, yes, what up? You're still outside. Yeah, I'm still outside. I'm outside too. Let's be mad mosquitoes out there
outside of logic
Outside of your argument yard
They spray for our mosquitoes we don't get too many and they don't like my blood
You got dirty blood?
Yeah.
Christine, they wouldn't bite you either.
Let me see this one go for you.
I think Smash isn't back again.
Get your blood filtered.
I use the blood product every week, so I think that's why
All right, you know here me now
What you're old-ass bitch play for your younger you'd be some
Mad from her kicking kicking
Friday night
Thank you very good
It's why you're so mad. What's going on?
Two days later, you're still upset about it, dude.
Well, it's your argument. Don't fuck with him, dude.
Two days later, you're still crying into your fucking pillow.
How am I crying? Oh, well, you just made the claim.
So the burden of proof would be on you, sir.
How am I crying in my pillow?
You're going off your cloak.
I did? What is this? You know, for the sake of argument,
I did get I did but now I know I know I paid now I'm here. What's your argument?
You're complaining you're going about Christine because she fucking
So what's your argument two nights ago two nights ago you kicked her okay then pay 60 bucks
Pay 60 bucks to kick me off go ahead
Why would I do that?
You're too stupid to fucking do it but go ahead
You're not gonna do it. You're too fucking retarded. You're too stupid. You don't have enough money. You're not gonna do it
I'm finna crash out because you know, you're not gonna do it
Sir, not only do you not you don't have enough money sir. You're too fucking stupid to do it sir
I'm gonna get a community community with a house and do it
Well, don't threaten us with a good time psyche wants it go ahead
Bucks and goes to go away forever go ahead six bucks. I'll go away
I'll go away forever go ahead
Christine this is my panel by the way. I paid for it, right?
Whenever this dude says says he's gonna crash out sucky went to my
It's after Christine's after this one is or like tomorrow or it's after
Or summer summer comes before that then I'll do some yeah, I gave a lot of money
We need to start this mission right after this one is it in
that's what I'm talking about right after that okay yeah we're gonna run it
oh my god what time does it end like you I'm gonna get my satisfaction at you
laughing with you with you sweetheart 1 a.m. I'm not gonna say up till 4
though I don't know I don't know maybe I will hold on
it's 146. So maybe we should end this at here, and then again it goes, give, yeah, and it goes, we'll leave it, it'll be open, but it goes, so leave it open, two to four, is that fine, or two to three, is that fine, two to three?
Yeah
Sike is that fine with you Sike I paid money is
Yes, all right, I don't know dick is money. Oh nice. We get some stage
Yeah, we need it. We need a lot of that a lot of it all the closer to the phone. Maybe he's asthmatic
I
Are you there LD? Oh, hey, what's up, say, okay, Gotti?
As your weekend on pretty good, bro, you weren't the socks. No, no, it's been like two or three days
Best socks ever
So I bought two smart TVs today my son unbox them, and I'll be damned one of them screens all broke
This is my bro on the first day
Well, we took out of the box. It was broken about they might have been used
Yeah
What make where they
Well, that's a big deal, but I don't need to use my fire stick or anything like that anymore because it's all built in
We're in like Amazon I'm zoned it and everything
And I'm cool TV
TV's are so cheap now. Yeah
that's like 200 bucks for the living room but and for the bedroom but I'm gonna take
the broken one I'm just gonna get my money back and buy a bigger one for the
bedroom you got it you see I put the five inch now for like yeah 85 is the way
to go yeah that's what I was looking at for my bedroom so I want to thank
Christine for sponsoring this next until 2 a.m. Pacific Standard Challenge
So, this is Christian.
I got you. I got you.
Thank you, Christine.
I'm going to start talking to this channel.
I'm going to support this team.
It's a wonderful one.
Thank you.
You're under Christine's thumb now.
Right.
I got two to three though.
It's all about me now, ghost.
Yeah.
I don't know. I don't know.
don't know. I don't know. I
We'll roast you
Well, go ahead and roast it for 11 more minutes. Go ahead
No, no between two and three
Go ahead
The crucible ghost
We need attention what a stater
No, I'm not in about ten minutes. Go ahead and roast me though
Christine you run in the panel
No, I'm just helping sponsor to keep it open
See if we don't sponsor to keep it open
He may decide to put the panel down and then where we go. I got you. I got you understand now that works
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I understand that
It's a good concept because
You can leave
Maybe
Don't fuck yourself. Go fuck yourself bitch. Didn't you shit?
For 24 hours I already paid you ain't gonna pay me ma'am. Go ahead
Sidi how much to bring your husband in here to bring
I
Pay more dumb dumb
Psyche where is psyche? Oh, I don't know but he needs to come up here. It's 25 so your husband
He did pay for this one, his title's over with, it is now Christine Heganalby's fucking block.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, the fucking block!
Why do you want to kick me for it?
You are no longer wanted on my page or nothing
Why my
Thank you back when it's his panel. That's all
He doesn't know how to be nice
I let him come to my panel and everything and I'll let bullshit last night because me and some girls were having some fun with each other
We weren't showing our tits a bunch of fucking guys. We were showing our tits to each other. So fuck him
Yeah
Yeah, I hate to crash out of the
chat. I'm going to miss some
shit. Yeah, goes back tomorrow.
We'll postpone your thing until tomorrow goes.
Yeah, we'll be up there. You prepaid, ghost. You prepaid. That's good.
Yeah, you can handle it tomorrow.
Thanks, ghost.
Yeah
We'll be fair like, you know, it's like
He did specify he's like, you know, it's this is not for like, you know, we're doing that
I was that was a courtesy that I was like, well, I'll still like, you know, name one for you
But that he never he told me that it wasn't for that. He was like, you know, and so it's like I tend to
Listen, he told you numerous time. It's just sure you do as you want with it
Yeah
It's not build a bear, you know
He's thinking that he gets like some kind of like power over it like the panel
It's like if you do sponsor the panel like yes, I will like probably you know, okay
I'm sure you probably nobody that would sponsor the panel would do anything that ever
Right now
Uh-huh. Put it right now. I'll put it in the chat. It's actually, um, let me see. I'll put it in the chat. Here we go. Um, cash out.
Right. I said I want to hang out with my friends for a little bit. I don't want to hear you're going to snuck a mouse right now.
I got to do it a lot of shit in the morning, and I just don't want to do it with them.
And I did tell everybody, send you prayers and good vibes. You're dealing with shit tomorrow.
Yeah, I hope everything goes well.
I put it on the screen.
Thank you.
that's why this 25 is worth it for me, right, thanks for the thing, by the way,
Um, yeah, it's like, uh, but yeah, I do have to still follow TOS and stuff like that.
And, you know, just by, you know, so like people, even if so, so, you know, I'm sure
that I think people sponsoring a panel will encourage them to even encourage other people
to behave in the chat sometimes too.
So, yeah.
Yeah.
So.
For good purposes. Okay, so you're in your low. Let's fight the symbols symbols is like I don't want to be a member
Yeah.
I'm like, I can't it was it's not it's not up to you. It's it's it's you too big side
So I do have 101 memberships right now. Wow, that's pretty awesome guys. Thank you. Congratulations
There are like over a hundred episodes at over a hundred shows on members only. I think I'm going to put most of the rest of them on members only.
Yeah, I'm not bringing themselves back. I mean, I'm like suspending that for the time being and it's kind of funny to the financial trolling, but it gets too complicated.
I 100% agree.
I don't know why I'm here on the end of it. I got it. I got it. I just send him money last night. I don't know why it's not coming. Thank you. The thing's gonna send you to 25. Thank you so much. Thank you so much. And that's for his band. Thank you.
Oh
So, okay, oh there she goes
Okay, so yeah, these glasses I can actually see really well in these glasses
So I really like I do like them because they're even better than the other ones are stronger
Print on the screen at least you're not blind like you'll be poor guy look at them. Oh, yeah, that's true
LD the guy LD doesn't like like, you know, I looked at mr. McEwan. I went to him
But he looks like you know, I dog and everything he looks like the archetypal
This is the Stevie Wonder, right?
It's like all done
Thank you so much
Yeah, but it's like those glasses look like Jeffrey Dahmer's
Play bottom it was Jeffrey down
It's like mostly black people they think they meet Jeffrey Dahmer there
I was like a person nickname that always be Jeffrey and so I just
Just playing up on it a little bit. I think you kind of liked it
But you said that did you hear that I was trying to get Jeffrey Dahmer glasses
You said those look like Jeffrey Dahmer glasses. They just do look like Jeffrey Dahmer glasses mission accomplished guys
I did it
Wow, you really want to be like a Jeffrey Dahmer. What was it? I don't want to I think it's kind of funny though
I don't even think Jeffrey Dahmer is like a real person personally. I think it's like a sigh up again, but
A whole boy was saying the same thing Jeffrey Dahmos
Thomas yeah
It's just like John Wayne Gacy. There's you know, John Wayne Gacy had 33 bodies buried under his floorboards
And I watched them all bring them in I'm checking out of the house
All these people with like sports jerseys with server numbers on them and stuff. It's just interesting
33 bodies you think that would like you know sink after a while, but no one's gonna miss 33 Cubs fans
Well, I don't know is that was that who they were there? It was the other I think it was like outside of Chicago
Yeah, but it was like and a lot of it is like a lot of it is like these serial killers
They'd like to have some gay twists to them always. It's even even the
You know the sh o o t er s like of the you know at schools
They like there was like a transgender one that was like an artist
I did like the shining I was drawing about the shining Jack Nelson all these are these weird like little little side
Oh, where'd everybody go? Let's see who just left. Um, I don't know, but yeah
Okay
Yeah
We gave her but but summers but this is summers avatars expecting and so there should be more coming
She needs to go to the gym more often. I'll be right back
Wake up for a second. I'll be right back
I told people in the couch watching a movie with the granddaughter and it's like
I gotta go to bed. I always wake myself up to go to bed. It makes sense.
I went to the movies last night to go watch. I know what you did last summer.
That was fun. Was it a good show? Is it a new one or is it the old cast?
No, it's a new one, but they had like Ready Prince Junior in it and Jennifer Love Hewitt
and stuff and even Sarah Michelle Geller. It's pretty good. I mean when they rated it wasn't bad,
but man, the new cast is terrible.
Very 90s very 90s cast sounds like yeah cast cool intentions or something. Yeah
Okay
You know anything about monetizing on tiktok because I thought it would take forever to get to like a thousand
Followers I think have how many do I have I have to I already have like 150 in a day. So I think not difficult
Um, you get a 10,000 you get monetized on it. I just don't know any much about it. So if anyone knows about any advice
I'm interested. Okay, so
Some might wait till she comes back. She might
I think we'll make a lot of money on there there's because of there's like a lot of people sometimes in the chats like a
And like you know that and they're kind of like more free-for-all kind of like you know a little bit
It's a little bit you know with a lot of graphics on the screen and like that kind of stuff, but I don't know
I don't know if I can come at the right material for this, but I
Could be looking I don't know. I think it's one of the better websites to stream on besides YouTube
Now just streaming or does tic-tac have panels?
I'm not really sure yet. I don't mean I I know you can take so I think people answer the phone and like
Connect with other people on tic-tac. You can like split the screen and do that like you can answer the phone
I've seen that before so maybe that's kind of like it, but I'm not 100% sure it's the same thing
There's actually one woman that like he makes half like I think she said she makes half a million dollars a year like she just
She presents
She's vegan and she goes into restaurants pulls down her pants and that goes
I'm shaking my yacht at the waiter and like you know
She just screams out and like cow boxers and like a like alien baby in our fake baby
And then she makes half a million dollars a year just for doing that. That's literally all she does
So that's kind of weird. Yeah
I'm just I'm saying people can be creative and like there's ways like to get really get an audience
Excited about you and stuff like that, you know, like I think that it's like the best
Best way to make money like besides like come out in many many years, especially doing what you want to do, you know, so
Yeah, pretty cool. He's on the panel right now. Let's see. I'm going to come. Oh, just
You see me
So I will see you tomorrow at 10 30 p.m. We'll start with your channel tomorrow, okay?
And that's a specific time. Yeah
That's every Cali yeah, exactly. I'm in so okay. We have to get four people. We're here. No
They're really small now. Okay, here we go
I want to come up on back chat. Okay. It's crucible though. That's what yeah both ghosts and he can't he's been banned for 24 hours. Oh
So we can hang in back chat or you can hang in regular chat, right?
Well, thank you this hangout. It's hangout it goes. It's just a little it's it's only a day away
Annie Annie to here's under somebody in back
It is oh, it's the same person it's who's will go see
Okay, so we're drinking this banana coffee right now. It's a cool. It's like a ice
Vietnamese banana coffee. It's like and it's like banana flavor coffee
And then it's like has like this really sweet root cream on it. And then I've also stulted caramel
Haven't you been drinking that for hours?
I mean, I drink Starbucks. Yeah this morning
Yeah, I drink Starbucks this morning and then but I was just in the mood for coffee
Okay, I like the release. Oh, this LD just disappeared. I like I like the really like, you know, the Vietnamese coffee is fucking good
I think it's much better than Starbucks. Actually, it's like you have a lot of it in LA. You have all these boba places, too
I don't like the boba. It's like these little like slimy. I'll say I there's one particular place near me
I love their watermelon boba. Oh my gosh. It's so good
Okay, yeah, I can imagine it being good fruity
But last one I had was like a coffee boba and so it was like all this
It isn't like it's a coffee caviar or something like that. It's just it's so weird
Now if this one and they have a pomegranate one too and that and you can get like a
watermelon the watermelon tea with pomegranate boba in it, and it's really really good
But only just one place I found that has a date all they do is boba
Wow
Yeah, they do have a lot of specialty places here now because they're you know, LA there's a just ton of like
Immigrants from everywhere. So there's all the best restaurants here
This is the only place I found with this Boba like this. It is so good. Oh my gosh
I'm gonna try
The fruit one. Yeah, just like in Starbucks, do they have these fruit drinks these like these are group freshers and nobody hard
I'm probably not all people get them, but they're really good
They also energy drinks for they discontinued them
Yeah, because that one college student died oh shit, but there was too much caffeine in her body
I'm going to assume a heart issue
And I was like, I used to take these caffeine pills.
You were taking no-dos, but I would take too many of them
and I would get so sick of it, look at them.
Well, my friend ends up with kidney stones
because of his energy drinks.
He hasn't been having any energy drinks
in detox to the body.
The coffee cause the kidney stones too?
It can.
Mm-hmm
I'm in it got calcium. I think in it calcium. Yeah
I
Mean they don't know, you know until somebody gets a kidney stone analyze
They don't know what the cause of it is or what kind it is
And by the time you know you have one it's like too late
I told my son I said that's the closest feeling yet to a woman having a baby. Just letting you know
Yeah, well, I mean women are savage people have kids
I think that's why women are better managing pain sometimes and men my dad was always like he likes double toe and really ah my mom could like you know
So it's like yeah women are I think women do have better pain management
Skill even though they feel they feel more, but they're also stronger in like
Well, I think it's coping
Mm-hmm. Yeah, it's like the mind is like, you know, able to
It's like selective hearing with pain or something like that. You know, I'm I'm a big baby
My stomach hurts. I'm just like I cannot
Well, I knew just like he walked out of the room the way he was doubled over
I knew a little kidney stone. He's like, I don't get kidney stones
It's like yeah the kidney stone
So he had to go to the ER and they did some tests and I get it's a kidney stone. I said so
And nothing does that other than lots of lots of water and flush it out
Well, yeah, but don't they do surgery for it to you like they can go in
Yeah, and they he's got several and they said one may not pass that he may need to have it taken out
But he didn't he says he doesn't have time to take off work. He got time for this
Mike okay
You're on the road a lot. I hate for this to happen
All your own world because if he doesn't have it taken care of you know, it would be too painful to work
I think for a little bit, right? Well, and he works a lot a lot of times out of state
I mean he does like seven different states. He's gone for one week at home for a week
So let's just hope it doesn't happen while he's on the road because
Mom is not gonna be there
Right. Yeah, I know, you know
psych
That's you know, what's the thing about parents, you know, they don't last forever so appreciate what you're here
That's why I like my son from my other son from New York down here for the summer. Oh
Really nice. Yeah, he comes down every June
With my granddaughters and then stays till mid-August he works from home
So he brings all his computer monitor
and his computer system, he does IT security.
Oh, cool.
That hospital system in New York.
Oh.
So he just works down here.
I have a room set up that he works in.
Cool.
Seems for the summer?
Yeah, for the summer.
And then I have my 12-year-old granddaughter down here
with us.
Are you doing? It's knocked over something. I'm not going to my phone and the water spells. Oh shit. I didn't break anything
Very good
Clean it up. You've been keeping your house clean. Clean it up. Yeah, my house is it's so good the bathroom
all the clothes are
This area so it took so so nice out here, but yeah
They psyche has suspended the bringing back
So once you're booted for 24 hours, you're booted for 24 hours.
Yeah, this works kinda.
If I put this right here, that kind of, that works, okay?
Perfect. Okay.
Nice. Yeah.
I mean, it's like, yeah, it was kind of, it was kind of entertaining.
And it's, of course, like, just like, the financial trolling is like, you know,
I don't think, yeah, after, after it all, if everyone's still blocked
and no one's really happy at the end of it, I wanna make sure everyone's happy.
And I'll be honest because I was one doing it in the way it was working. I was not very happy
And I don't look noticed but just for me to shut my mouth. I'd enjoy panel for a few days. I got you
I got you and I
Understands and that's I know that's why I was going to considerations of like, you know
I just want to make sure everyone feels that everything's fair and everything so but but it was a it was interesting a test run and I was
You know, I was able to get a new tablet for the show and stuff and so, you know
And then when I got that I was able to get more into the AI and so now you see all the AI I'm doing stuff like that
and so
It makes it like it makes it easier to do that stuff
And so that really does help to show too because I think well, I'm plus and no offense, but
Not everybody can keep track of who did what because I guarantee you that day
It wasn't accurate on who did what so that makes a problem too when
You got people going back and forth and you you don't keep track
Mm-hmm, and that was an issue too. Yeah, I'm gonna keep better track and
You know I have my little notebook now, and I will be more on top of it. You know, I'm really concerned about
keeping the show
good and fun and
No
And bear and so I will
Keep better track. I know I have work to do
Little bit, but I'm I think I'm improving I do and I'm trying to improve so thank you guys for bearing with me
Okay, oh
Shit, so yeah, that's why I didn't join because I didn't want to open my mouth
Well, I I love when you I love when you speak and you know, I don't know why
Anyone would have an issue with you, but oh, I don't care people issues with me. You know that, right?
Yeah, I can't like everybody all the time and if you don't have haters not doing something, right?
Yeah, and you're but you're such a sweetheart, you know, it's because yeah, no
Okay, I'm not a sweetheart am I
Okay, never mind. Yeah, no, I can be if I choose to be
Right. And what certain people I am. Yeah
Yeah, other people not so much
Yep
And like I said, if you don't have the haters, I mean because you gotta have the haters along with the lovers
You know this
Have to have them both. Yep. There's two sides of the coin and it's like, you know
Yeah, you can't appreciate one without the other either, but yeah, I can appreciate haters
But you know appreciate your but that love you more when you see like you know how people that don't it can act sometimes though
It's really good coffee, I'm so good, okay
Hey, say turn why are you not up here?
KT get your ass up here Marcy get your ass up here
are you going to bed or are you getting up here. Okay you come up to stay get your
ass up here. Jamie get your high knee up here.
Money money get your honey up here ghost isn't back. I'm afraid to look at the backchat. Go. I think ghost is back there
There's 26 private chats back there. I'm afraid
Not no importance
Okay
Okay, I was impulse the dinosaurs
Which one would you like to discuss?
And which ones are extinct in which ones, you know, we have some that could be dinosaurs
and probably warped one time down down in south Florida um i'm gonna get cold they fall out of
the trees onto your head one's your ride back in the day darn you know i wish i was back there
in that day i really do i think that would be quite exciting to own a dinosaur not sure where i
Might fit in my backyard. I
Never really written one I
Think I only have it on the Flintstones. I'm not sure though. Yeah. Oh, we could do yabba-dabba do
Money hit the link honey. Mm-hmm, you know zen pulse I take it all with a grain of salt, you know that, right?
I can be the old right-of-head or I can be the person that talks or I could just be whatever
Talk about my kids grandkids. I know it's all jokes and posts like I said, I take it with a very green assault
Yep, Marcy's head a near-death experience mm-hmm
That's a few of them today.
Wow.
Um, yeah, I talked to somebody named, I don't know if you ever saw the oceans deep blue.
She is a psychic on a on YouTube and she's been on my show a few times.
And yes, she told the whole story one time about her premonition about being this car accident
and then when it actually happened and all this, I mean, so, and she also had, you know,
went to another realm and saw people and all kinds of interesting stuff.
You know, you've heard me talk about numerous times of deaths in the ER, how the ring gets
and what we've seen and just...
Well, I know that there is, I mean, there's this famous story I've seen about this cat
and that there's a, it was a retirement home or like a nursing home and this cat would,
Only like right before someone died the cat a couple days before where they go in their room and they sit on their bed
And so then that would kind of alert the nurses of the person's about to die
And the person would always die if the cat could sense it
Isn't that crazy, you know, I know I've heard of that before
I've heard of that
Yeah, I mean
They're very they're very intuitive. Okay, so hold on so summer here's summer summer
What's up, everybody? Hey
Thanks for
About in that black. I just have like Dylan's shit. I have to last night
You're looking for me
I don't know if he's drinking something harder down
Starting drinking early. I don't know what his problem is, but he is just nasty
Oh
Did have a lot of fun last night on the show. That was a lot of fun
Yeah, and we were having fun and what was crazy is this motherfucker wants to sit here and act like we were sitting here showing boobs
To like guys and shit dude. We were showing our boobs to each other or you're like
Tuck over yourself and you weren't even showing boobs
No
Showed you didn't have her entire top off with her hand over it
That that was a little risque, but it's not you know nothing nothing
We were still doing it to each other me and spunky were doing it to each other
You know because we're both we've both got big boobs and we were like boobies
You know me
We all got fucking man. We ain't up here showing our shit's a bunch of fucking losers
We're gonna show it ourselves to each other. It gives a fuck
Yeah
It was it was fun though. Yeah, yeah, we did have a good time until he came up a fucking round it like and so he is
It's yeah, it's funny like some I don't know. Yeah, some people will never
He's never really happy. I wanna hear him like just happy with him. I think he always think he always sounds kind of pissed off and
imagine me, but oh
Well, look at me. It gets down to let y'all it needs to fuck it fucking glow key
We were having a good time.
Yeah, come on, I'll just come up and have some fun.
It was fun.
And I wasn't showing cleavage because I didn't have any to show,
but it was fun watching you ladies have laugh and have a good time.
Yeah, we actually had fun.
You were laughing.
I mean, the chat was laughing.
Yep.
Yeah, but it's like so yesterday I saw like there's a there is a your cue had done this like his show and it was called
Pay me to hang out or pay me to talk to me. And then and I was like, okay
So and then he's like, oh you're just charging people now to talk to you
He's like and he's like how about they tell what they charge how about you charge them whenever you stutter
And then he was just so mad like screaming that and then it's like he just like stood for like the next hour
He was just like staring at the camera
They kind of like with a piss-off look and then he then him then Joe Schiffley called in and like they talked for like
That was the whole show. I'm like, okay. Well
Don't know. He's but it was so funny. He's it means like the guys like who are you talking about? He's like, oh, if you don't know
I'm talking about you don't know nothing. I think wow. I'm really
Canada when were you on crack?
I was talking about psych
Yeah, you don't get to give any money back. Oh, you're done for 24 hours homie. Fuck you
Go as you said that it that was not even for the the sponsoring. I mean it's like and no I
was like well, but even when we sponsor
It wasn't for that. He specifically said numerous times
It's for you to do as you please with
And I have that on I have that on on tape goes so
Yeah, we all heard it even. He's a drug. He's a drug bastard. You can't remember shit
We know yeah
He was BB's slave now. Oh
Okay
Did I call you well, and I don't know what time you called. I was busy with um the TVs right you the new TVs
We got we were trying to put up. Oh
Summer got I got my daughter glasses summer look
To heck look at those. Yes. Those are daughter glasses
Those are definitely daughter glasses
Can you see with them?
Yeah, they're there. They're a little bit stronger than the other ones. I think they're like two two times magnified or something like that
So yeah, that's you really well. Okay. I was like
I was like can I get your ass up here? What do you why are you smoking crack? What happened?
Yeah, he's been removed from panel because of this behavior.
Summer, he was telling people that he was just jumping around.
But he said he was telling people that I was eating my own vomit online,
and people were coming in to the chat saying, oh, are you eating your own vomit?
And I'm like, what is this about?
It's just a disgusting suggestion that would make people say, oh my god,
they're just like make people say, you know.
So, I don't know. There's no reason really to say that and I
Wouldn't let it go easy. He said it numerous times
Yeah, I don't know what was going on with that
I was just making sure because I'm like, I know I know Canada
You know to me and like and yes, he can be a hot mess at times for sure
But when I seen him talk about smoke crack, I was like, hold on what? Oh stop the press
So, okay, he was just joking on that. So all right never run
We see Fred and he's he turned on me. So
Oh, Canada. Oh, Canada. I don't know. Okay. It's okay. It's okay. But I am, I am redoing
all the, I mean, I'm going to redo the members graphic, just because I don't, you know, I
don't think he'll want me using his, his graphics anymore. So I switch you on to all my graphics.
Right Shay he was even saying Sykes cats. Don't get fed and they eat
But I would the whole thing was crazy
What I think please tell me what I say
Anything I have to say I say it to him. So, you know something fuck you
And why don't you look at what Shay even said just saying
You're going
Late how are you gonna explain like what are you gonna explain like it was a joke?
Okay, she's it's a joke, but then you were like saying it over and over again, and I don't know
He was obsessed with it
Well
Not very nice camera. Oh, look at this graphic. I made home. This is pretty cool
Yeah, it's like my talker ish. Well, but with your worst stuff on it. Yeah, it's cute
Hopefully I don't know. I just found this in like some program. I downloaded. I forgot I made it so maybe I'll try to
Yeah, like I like
The active backgrounds
Katrina does a couple for me. I really like those since they let them let us do them
Let's see if it works on my stream yard right now. Let me see stream yard
Yeah, that'd be
They move for it to 130
That's so weird
The only thing I can think of is maybe they caught wind that we were getting support up there at nine and so they thought they'd switch it, but
Now we do it switch our support time. So
Why do you think people won't be there?
See I don't know if people will be there, but I know we'll be there. So that's all that matters
I hope people show up tomorrow. I do. I bagged everybody in there. Fuck a mama
Wow
Come here pussy
He is making fun boy once he hides, thank you. Hi
It's court supports impulse there's a sentencing tomorrow and what though
Prosecutors suggest he is absolutely absurd and totally
My friend was murdered by a cop and they're
Suggesting that the cop gets one day, which he had 45 minutes in jail when they booked him
But they're suggesting one day Tom served and a hundred dollar fine
That's what happened for anybody don't know we're going to court for them
Since it's in tomorrow, so we'll see what happens
Wow
Good luck
Can the dry why did you keep getting put in back because of the bullshit you were saying about psych when you were told ten times to stop
Think about that one
I hope so zip look pause pause. I don't know how to say your name, baby
Simple then pause then pause, okay
Happy fucking everybody's names up
Everybody we have a nice point 51 people in chat awesome guys
Are we all doing? I had two choices. I could have came woke up and chose violence and then just wrecked your panel all fucking night long
Which I thought about doing I'm not gonna lie and apologize and later, but then I was like, you know what?
That's not gonna put me in the right mindset. I was like, let me just chill
smoke a plant if I can chill cuz
I'm ready yelling and screaming when I'm yelling and screaming. That's when you know, I'm okay. That's all I'm gonna say
When she gets quiet so we have a concert
Yeah, I always say whenever everyone gets quiet. I'm like where the I was always get suspicious in the voices of my head go quiet
right
I'm allowed mouth. I like talking shit. Well, I'm quiet
I love my
Okay
Okay, so I can't just trying to talk to me Christina's okay
Trying to tell me what let me see she was like the video made of me eating his own bomb here. Oh, hold on
So there's a video of me that somebody made
Okay. Well, that sounds disgusting. Okay
So there's a video of you eating the barf Kate played it. Also. He did bot make that up
No, he did not make that up. There's not a oh
I okay, so I'm eating vomit in a video. Sure. Sure. Sure. Sure. I just
Guys are ridiculous. Is there a video or something out there? That's doing that. I think is that think that's what he's selling you
Well, that's the case and they should come up to the back chat put the link in
In the back chat, there's no video of that because that never happens. I mean, it's like what I never threw up and then
Well, I mean somebody could make an eye somebody could make a AI video for sure 100%
And I think that's what Canada's trying to tell you guys that he's not talking shit. Hold on. Let me finish
He's not talking shit that there's a channel that has actual videos of Psyche saying this shit
That's what I'm taking it as I could be wrong
Or may well be accurate I don't know
But he got put be to put him in the back at least
I'm estimating ten times because she told him to stop talking shit about Psyche and he wouldn't
Yeah, but if he's not talking shit and he's trying to tell you guys that there's a channel because he's even telling money
To go get the channel and share the link
But even he was even talking about how his cats aren't fed his cats aren't taking care
Again, you're not hearing me. I really this is the best thing to do
Canada go get the link and bring it up here and drop it up here on the back chat
He's he's not talking shit. He's telling you all there's a channel that is saying this
That's what he's saying. I wouldn't even believe a video if I start
So that's not what he was doing that night summer. Yeah, I know it was because I know there's no video like that
And it's like and so it's like yeah, it's hard question for summer
Huh, huh, he mailed me the email me the link Canada
Summer I have a question about your friend
Hello, which I ended up got you said wait, so you're your friend was murdered by a cop
Yeah, it's not something I'm gonna talk about on this panel was he an African-American
I'm not gonna talk about this on this panel. Was he really murdered by a cop?
You know what happened in the fucking seconds that I click the link. What's going on?
I get him off
The cop was found guilty bottom line. I don't want to talk about it
Because all he's gonna do is make racist fucking jokes. I ain't feeding into this bullshit. He knows who the fuck I'm talking about
Yeah, hear me. Yeah
We hear you
Yeah, there was a video that so what's kind of nasty so yeah
You go to sleep man
And be the same he was venting because he was kicked off stikies
That was before I get all that better you guys listening to what 420 is saying y'all are like and I love y'all to death
But I know y'all don't like fuck with Canada, but you got to hear out what they're trying to say
I really don't believe Canada sitting around talking shit
I think he's trying to tell y'all that there's a channel out there that's talking like my shit even 420 is coming up and saying it
So let's take the job like and that's cool if y'all don't fuck with Canada. I don't give a fuck that's on y'all
You know what I mean? I don't care. I'm just saying like
Are y'all not listening?
Well, but no, I'm listening, but let's take the vomiting away and let's put the point of how he's telling everybody he's not taking care of stand.
I want to see the link because that way if this is what the channel is saying,
Well, I don't know what channel it came from, but somebody dropped a link to it yesterday.
Can I explain something, Summer?
Yeah.
And then if you guys want to see it, like, whatever, but I just want to explain to Summer because
I was on a panel and I didn't want, I wasn't there to talk shit about Psyche, you know,
me and him, you know, it's just like, I don't want to know if he did a boo boo or even did
throw up and eat it.
I don't think.
whatever. I didn't want to watch it. So I just didn't want to hear from it at that moment
because I also was drinking and I didn't want to get sick and I just thought that psyche is not
there to defend himself. But I'm not saying that it's happened or it didn't. So that's all I wanted
to explain to you. That's why I kicked them. It wasn't because because I just didn't want to watch
it. You know what I mean? At that moment.
Yeah, right and I get that 100% and like I said, I mean, I don't Canada can be Canada. I'm not you know, whatever
I just think in this particular thing. He's saying that hey, there's a video out there that there this is what it's doing
I like kind of dry. I like, you know, um, there is moments, a lot of times he's like very, he's, you know, chill and he's harmless, but that night he was really, really angry at psyche and he just kept on every time I was like, okay, can we move on?
And we had a bunch of other people on the panel, but he just wanted to talk about that every time, you know?
Like did you pay him for the work he did for you? Did you pay him for those graphics?
He said that there were there were courtesy. I mean he was like he he said they were a gift, you know
And we talked about so yeah, that was a nice gesture
So it's weird that he would be talking shit about you on somebody's pal
I I believe that that he did if they're saying he did if Peter said he did I believe it
But yeah, Christine was there a lot of people were there and it was out of character because he's normally not like that, you know
Maybe you had a bad day.
All right, so I have the video.
I have the video.
Okay, just so you all know.
I'm gonna put it. I'm gonna have to come back down. I got the video
That's a nice deal to make
Sounds like what it was said is like I was maybe asleep and so I don't
Don't bring my second thing up in the back. I'm just gonna drop a leak. Okay. I thought I talked shit about psyche every day
It wasn't like him talking shit just it was just like I don't fucking see a video of anybody throwing up
I feel like we're gonna watch that movie um stand by me and everybody's gonna start throwing up at the same time
That's a kind of drop it's like it's like
It sounds like I was asleep. Okay, so if I'm asleep, it's like are you really gonna like, you know
I'm obviously not conscious at that time, you know
Yeah, but he didn't make the video somebody else made the video
Whoever made the video fuck them
Exactly. That's what I was saying. I'm sorry. Don't give it life. That's all. Well, and like I said, you can take that part out of it completely. He was doing nothing about the comp. There were 10 people on panel were all trying to talk about different things. He kept going back and and ramming site. All right, videos on the back. Okay, thank you so much.
Yeah, I was like, I was like he doesn't take care of his cats. I was like they look fine to me
And that we ought to call the animal control and he was saying all kinds of stupid shit
People gonna say shit man. His friends were gonna believe
Well, he told summary was not smoking look at him beat look at him beat the cat
Look at him how he beaten that cat poor cat. No, you leave that cat alone
And that's what I told them I was like anybody that's gonna call like animals like control on those cats is crazy
Because there's only like homeless cats out there and these cats are taking care of and they're just gonna laugh at them anyways
You know, that's what you told them because he kept trying to get everybody to call animal control on psyche
I guess you can explain that to candidate dry, right?
maybe
He was venting. I don't know. I'm just being honest and Christine is a lying and HK is no one I swear at the power
You're you're got your mics covered psyche this this mic's been bad all night. Yeah
Meanwhile Christine is on of like a bullhorn
I'm on my phone
It's just my phone
Nothing more. What more do you want me to say?
You guys hear me now hear me now. Yeah. Yeah, that's okay
Yeah, I'm Canada dry you're able to see whatever you want in the chat like I know it's like
You're mad at me. I'll be backstage because you were annoying me one night, you know, just like
Singing song is like out of the blue like really annoying and just like being all
I'm like, I don't know. You're just like had this mug look on your face. I saw that night because I do random guy
You don't like it. Oh, oh
I'm a psyche angel
He said why this summer got so much to pull around here cuz we're psyche's angels
And we got money
I love
My friends of the show and
You're kind of a coin or I know it's like my tablet
So I thought it was God again
Not me these are teemo tablets
No, this is well this one's that I'm on my iPad my Apple iPad and
One of a better tablet the fight the firetabler pretty much sucks
That's good. That's good. Okay good sounds better
Yeah, so
Caramel coffee to drink look at this coffee. It's really good. Oh shit
But yeah, I was listening to the chat and Vietnamese coffee or a frickin bomb, but they're like they'll keep you up for like three days
Mix it with
Yeah, oh yeah, the other one was banana it was
Doing it's like he's always like I'm going through like the storm or tornado or something
Anyway, what happened with the ghost guy?
Last night, we were all up here, all the girls, we had a full girl panel except I think Gotti
and Chris was up here, right, but they weren't just chilling, it was just, they were letting
the ladies be the ladies, right, me, Spunky, Paige, Marcy.
You know, he's up here. We, you know, taking our boobs, showing a little cleavage at each other.
No one else, no dudes. We really were showing our boobs to each other. I get all kinds of people
watching whatever, but we were showing our boobs to each other. Like, we weren't doing that shit to
anybody else. And then Ghost just went on this fucking two hour rant about how I was a whore
and my husband, you know, I'm doing this shit behind my husband's back. Mind you,
my husband's sitting literally right next to me. The whole fucking time because I'm in my fucking her.
Yeah, you should probably mind cuz we didn't get to see the the you know the boobies
He hates women yeah, he hates women dude when he's drunk he hates fucking women and mind you I let him come to my
You know, he's not wanted in too many places anymore cuz he gets the fucking annoying with his dumb dumb fucking
I'm gonna debate you conversations
Right and and everybody gets sick of a shit, but I let him come to my channel
I'll let him hang out. I love all that shit and he wants to sit there and just do shit like that when he gets fucking drunk
So fuck him dude. I didn't feel like doing tonight. So
You think ghost is gay and he's in love with psyche. I think he's nothing
I think he just is one of those people that just doesn't do anything
No, because he's like, uh, he definitely supports psyche a lot. So I don't know
I might I think he might have a crush on psyche
Oh, he's paying for it. You mean all the money's thrown at the woman because he's kind of
No, that's the thing ghost ain't even good at that at least you know at least
Money around fuck it. You know what I mean? He can't even do that. That's the first time I've seen him since he's been on fucking youtube give money to anybody
I'm not gonna get a twist
Yeah, he does
But Alex will play that's why he gets away with some of his bullshit
That's it exactly
Ghost he was just a little too late. He thought that little $10. He was doing a super chat yesterday was really gonna do something
Well financial troll baby level the fuck up. Listen, we all pick on each other man. We pick on dudes
We pick on girls. I mean, it's the same shit. You got to keep it even but you can't just focus that fucking you just he's like laser
Focus on women all the time. It's like just yelling. Yep. It's just fuck
but i do agree with canada dry in the chat saying that okay he was out of character but
they do or everybody lets alex get away with a lot more fucking shit that he said like crazy
ass shit i agree with that too i do agree with that alex gets away with a lot well psyche had a
question i think canada gets on people's nerves for whatever reason and so there's a shorter rope
Yeah, the baby with him
You saw he saw the baby
Yeah, it was half page half psyche half Alex
Poor page
Okay, Alex is definitely worse
They needed a surrogate so because they can't have kids so they have to use a beautiful woman like page and she yeah
I guess you would happen. Okay. I got you
Hidden away
From these friends, I know right thank God
We got a protect page
Money thanks for gifting
Shout out to 420 for the membership. Oh, Jamie don't laugh Jamie. Just you know, just chill
Don't laugh you're not allowed to laugh Jamie. I know laughing
You just gotta be there you can't nobody laughs. I'm gonna be very serious
Well, I just wanted to come up for a little bit oh there he is
thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank
the
end of the
Thank you so much.
My bad, my bad. I got stuck on another page.
I was trying to get back to the stream though.
I got you.
So
Yeah, the page in Alice video is she has a five o'clock shadow in the video. There's also some weird androgynous
Being hanging out in the corner. You see that? Yeah, what happened with that?
I took that and I was looking and she had a fucking shadow like a little beard. I was like, why don't they each have a beard?
Yeah, Alex has so much testosterone that he just passes it on to the woman and she turns into a man eventually
That's just me. It was me it was me in drag trying to fool him thinking that I was crazy. And
He's still the worst thing he saw
Yeah, and uh, it worked. It worked just saying you have an echo psyche. Oh, okay. I should hold on one second
I'm going to hop off. It was
No
We don't want the bad bugs bite ignore it ignore it. Okay. Okay, so let's
Okay, one minute. Okay money for 20. How's everyone doing 1147 almost midnight and wishing our no
That's not middle of the night. What time is the wishing hour 3 a.m. Or midnight depends on the closely. Yes
Okay
Everyone good?
Anybody do anybody
Yeah, so you don't want to let you don't want to let Canada up to explain for two minutes
Canada has explained himself, and he eventually I succeed. I mean, it's like I know maybe he'll apologize
I'll unban him from the studio, but I really if you don't want it. Don't do it. I'm just saying you know put it to bed
I mean, I he's a he's I bet I unbanned him
Two minutes, maybe you're
I
Don't think he wants my forgiveness. Yeah, he'll just do it again. It's like I don't think he likes me very much
It's a problem. I think so there was a time when someone slapped him off
Okay, he's here. Hold on. Yeah, if he doesn't like you then fuck off
I'm gonna put up the banner real quick. We'll get get clarity once and for all. That's it. He's not gonna porn bomb you
Well, it was like I said it was more than him just talking about the bomb
Christina's up here with so many
Shit about so many things all the time and then I do it once
and i'm like right i was gonna say there's a lot worse shit that gets said on this panel
i just think he gets on y'all's nerves that's why y'all don't like him and that's whatever but
i mean there's a lot worse shit said on this panel than anything has ever said in my opinion
and and on that christine please don't interrupt me and let me speak um so yeah yesterday when i found
that fucking channel that was like trash talking you and not just you i was trying to let other
There's Christine's up there fucking Marcy's up there for everybody's up there
And so that's why I came in and I said hey everybody if I were you
I would try to cam up as little as possible because somebody's recording everyone
I don't have to give you
No, no, that's what I'm trying to explain to you is that you were told I can't talk
Okay, so what about telling people to call animal control on the cats?
Is it gonna take you an hour or is it gonna take you two minutes?
Go ahead Canada
No
Because it's it's like impossible every time I open my mouth shut up and speak
Yeah, I I don't think I can with you up here, okay, then step down then step candidate
That is saying what you were saying just gonna say what you're saying. Oh, okay. We were saying
Come on Canada
Where so where was I?
You're talking about
Yes, I said to someone I was like yo you guys should stop like camming up on here because people are recording you guys and then someone's like
Oh, Canada's threatening us, and I'm like I'm not fucking threatening anyone
I'm letting you guys know that someone's fucking doing weird shit, and then
I came up on here and
When I said all this shit somebody
and blocked me and then I went away and then I went over to beat us here and I
yeah I said all that I was like all the cats fucking biting psyche on here so
psyche didn't feed his cat but I said a bunch of shit I was just I was I'm not
gonna lie
The whole fucking thing just got me like turnt. I was a little hyper. Yeah, which I rarely am
You know what I mean?
And I kind of went off and I can apologize for going off but fuck man
I've seen people do way crazier shit on here and then all I was trying to do was tell you about the whole thing
But because people kept fucking
Basically ignoring it or pushing it to the side or instead of listening to what I was saying attacking me personally
It just I just went off. I just fuck
Nobody wanted to hear you and you were told by the channel owner
That's right, nobody wanted to listen to you and you insist on people listening to you
Right because you're all being posted on another channel Christine so whether you want me to
We know that whenever we're on panel
I can guarantee you I can guarantee you I can get a video of you talking that night
Guarantee you
That's fine. That's okay
What I said
Oh, no, I'm going to get the video to prove to you. You were not doing it just to warn people
You know, well, let's finish this
Very hyper and started acting a sweetheart it's happened this didn't happen
It literally happened the same night
You know what? Forget forget. I brought you last night. I brought you last night.
And Bita was not live yesterday at all.
So it was not the same fucking day even. So there's that.
Okay, Christine.
Well, you know where you started wrong Canadian was bitching and complaining that people were recording. This is YouTube people are always recording.
Okay, you like psych right you like them. Don't you I got no problem with psyche
How does that my private video if it's like if it was a be recording me sleeping or something like that
It's like not somebody like else coming in putting like taking a video of me putting it up
It's like my own videos not like no not if your videos psyche if your videos on your channel are private for members only
But they're viewable on someone else's
They're viewable and rumble, and rumble sometimes indicates it.
And they're live.
Do you not understand?
There are people that are recording this right now.
What's your point, Christine?
There are people that record the lives as they're running.
But Christine, what's your point?
My point is you're an ass and you're lying.
So I will get the video to prove it. I'm not but I'm not lying. I will admit to anything
So why is it when you were asked numerous times to stop you didn't?
was hyper and fucking going off we all do it sometimes so why is it you were also trying
to get people to call animal control on site I don't think I've ever tried to get anyone to
call I'm getting the video I will get the video I will get the video all right right on Christine
Watch me.
I don't give a fuck.
Well, yeah, you do.
Anyways, like, uh, yeah, no, I've got no issues with you, buddy.
And no, I don't need payment for the small logos I made for you.
I just, but yeah, no, that, that is what happened.
Um, okay.
I was going off on it, but we've all like
Like said shit about each other like I've come on panel and and heard you guys say different things about different people
Whatever, I'd never do that. I got hyper when I saw those videos, and I think I just started going off
So anyways if I offended anyone, I'm sorry, but I am offended
Okay, I'm just and apparently Shay is offended and he man's offended what I like
Was offended or she wouldn't have put your ass in back numerous times
I can't
I'm just gonna say here
No, I have that much power over you. You just told me I do though
You told me that I make you feel something and that's awesome. No, I don't you don't I think you're a loser
Keep feeling some type away. I I can feel your loser all I choose. Yeah. Yeah
I'm not a grandmother who spends 24 seven online with a bunch of people and I'm not an unemployed
20-something-year-old living with mommy me neither
So I don't know who is is that you're obsessed with the girlfriend
To do that you don't do you don't know what you're talking about
Of course, I don't I know nothing you you really are pretty yeah
Oh
Are you done
Depends if you're gonna talk because I may not let you talk the rest of the time
Let's put this to rest because I can I can talk anytime I choose it
All is forgiven, you know, it's okay. I don't care what you said about me. I don't
I don't care I don't care really
I really don't tell me love. I want to know why I talk shit secretly like with me and
Brad talked shit about you. We told you he was gonna go
Secretively ask me something right now and I will confirm or deny it. I will not why are you gay?
I am not gay.
How long have you been gay?
Ah, fuck.
I'm not gay.
I don't know.
It was like a fleeting second.
By the time I thought about it, I remembered I wasn't gay look look you wouldn't come here if you didn't like psyches, right exactly
I come I wouldn't have made logos for psyche
That's that time we got along but then it's like you they kind of turned on me and nothing's happened dude
I've been gone for a couple months working and
Nothing
Yeah, you totally want
Ego about you
Are you taking drugs dude me? Yeah all the time marijuana Canada
Just smoking weed and working taking care of my grandma weed. It's definitely the weed
Yeah, it is he gets more high than me. I'm jealous the Canadian weed is fucking laced. It's fire
We do a good job up here
Well, that's settled. What's next?
Well, don't just whopper. Let's see the next case
Oh, I don't know
Oh, yeah, well thanks
Ramen beef noodles and then I put hot sauce on
Hot sauce in the noodles
My my my shit with ramen
It's a big Dallas. He got it to cook through the vlog of the morning. I'll be like a good
Do you ever put an egg in there? I guess what I was gonna say an egg. That's really good
We're gonna hit egg in the hot water
Do you like me like like fried or do you like hard boil it?
I put it raw, but then I put it in like the hot boy the boy like the boiling
Yeah, yeah
I like the hot water to cook it.
I'm doing it, I'm going to ask ChatGPT to draw a picture of Lenore, it's like drawing it right now.
I'll put it up when I get it.
ChatGPT is really cool, like now it does, it can put videos, this video is drawing, oh, okay.
But uh, okay. Well, Canada's ride. Thank you for explaining yourself
Yeah, you don't have to ever use my logos either if I gave you
Tee-tee, what's the best recipe for robin noodles? Let's see if some
Thank you for explaining
You've been
So I'm just pretty basic. I just like my noodles with hot sauce on them.
I don't eat them.
Hold on.
Where is it?
Who did it?
But there is a good person now that you can make out of Robin Nugos.
If anyone wants to, if the person that did it would like to step up for a cab, they can sit if they don't need to.
I'll give it an anonymous if they want me to keep it up.
What happened?
He was clapped.
Now, that's part of the game.
Where are you getting all these laughs from I have a little soundboard every little every little soundboard
I'm way from the phone and I hear these laughs. I'm like, what the hell I
Have
Yeah
Somebody's working with a sound board
Yeah, if they get a little sound board, I know I'm trying to like find better
Down effects that I can use for the right purposes. I don't know. We got a little actually I'm okay
Longer chords for my my headphones and my my tablet so
I'm uh, I'm able to like move around a little bit more now, so and I won't lose my headphones anymore. So that's good
Stay and have it. Okay. Let me see if chat if you need to my picture of my cat one second
Oh
Okay, I mean they did but oh who's the kitty cat summer's kitty cat. Yeah, they did it
But it's like I don't think it was a good picture of Lenore. See what you guys think
Yeah, oh the other one. Yeah, this one is kind of like a curtsy this one that I just had a teppy to
Draw this one and they drew this here
Oh that Lenore she had a little fireplace and I like the other one better this one. Hold on. This one's better, huh?
Oh or this one
Pretty cool. Yeah guys I also
Updated the emojis. I have as many as I can use I think I can have 14 right now
So I get some more people but
You know has a suggestion for me to replace any of them or one you would like or something that you think could be of use in the
Chat just let me know okay
Let me turn on the glass
Okay, so I must bid everybody do because I need to get back to bed now
Good night, Christine. I love you. Thank you so much. I'm sure I will see you tomorrow
Night everybody good night
Yeah, yeah cat cat GPT. Yeah cat, you know, yeah cat is cat in French. I think right
or
the shot let's see there
The noir the oh, yeah
The noir
Means the night right the nor is like la noir machine tonight in French
Oh, yes Canada dry you I'm not gonna say who did it, but yes, it was somebody did donate to
Clap you for 24 hours this time. I
Oh, okay
What's that terrible crying noise, okay, you hear that?
Okay
Money, how are you money?
I'm falling asleep. I'm just listening to you. Okay. I'll see you at Lullaby.
No, I'm good. 94 12. I don't need a Lullaby. I smoke a blunt. That's all I need. Okay. Okay.
Well, sweet dreams. Sweet dreams.
Have a good night.
Okay
Oh
God are you playing music? God are you playing a boy?
I don't know
There's a voice of some woman crying God he's playing guy. He's not playing sound effects like that. I hear you. I know it's you
That's not me. You're so smart. It's not me. Is that a porno? No
It's either someone crying or
Bow-how the crying porno. Yeah, she's crying. She had bad sex. She's crying
That your left girlfriend
It's what it's one of those bad points. Okay. Bye, Gotti. Oh, you turn it off. Okay. Oh
I hear it still
Oh, that was me. I said, oh, no, don't cry. Don't cry. That wasn't that wasn't that wasn't your voice summer
I could tell and I
Don't be very good here. That's got it. It's actually got his that's got his real voice
No, sir. Yeah, I was very sad
He's actually Rosie O'Donnell's next god wept
He was hard-frogged over Canada. Yeah, poor guy. Yeah
Well, you know, oh God had an emotional side, didn't you 24 hours?
I would hope so. I mean
I would hope he does 24 hours. Yeah
24 hours ago
I know it's not nothing like, you know, I wasn't really even mad
I was just like sometimes I sometimes I get annoyed with people and then I like something hey
Hey, it's my panel. I get to like, you know, keep people off and stuff if I get a noise
I have that's the power of your show. So, yeah
Everybody
You put me in a bag here so when I was going after what you fucking ass face look of it
It's editing it's just a little editing, you know, it's like I'm trying to like I have to be the editor producer writer
Oh, I mean, you know, you know, it's hard in a creator
It is it is it's not the easiest, but I'm still learning. I'm gonna get better, right?
Yeah, you're right. You're good prices. Yeah. Yeah, I'm gonna
Here come on tricks you want to see come on. There's my little in my little unhappy kitty. Are you my little unhappy kitty? Oh
your little oh
That's not oh
You hear that hurry hurry
Like she was like, what was that?
God are you to behave yourself don't make fun of tricks behave. What is this behave shit?
Little tongue
Hmm cats tongues are rough, right? They're they're all like scratching shit. Yeah, like stamp paper your little stamp paper time
Yeah, that's my nose sometimes when I'm sleeping he wakes up by licking my nose
They have that so they can lick the shit off their ass. Oh come on, please
No, it's for the
Little hooks on their tongue to get their hair like
Hair and they have a hairball if they do it's not for the shit on their butt
Oh, yeah, okay. What do they do scrub their ass against the floor dogs do that?
No, I catch the cats. Well, they don't like it, but this like, you know, they like other stuff too, but you know
Yeah, but you know
I mean dogs do too and people like you know kiss their dog in the mouth
I got to be up at six in the morning. Don't fall asleep. I'll be back and show okay
Good night. March 24 20. Have a good night
Later 20. Yeah
Gareth, I'm just the real simple country boy. I ain't got to cap my sins. I came a long way to get right here
I don't know. I ain't afraid to do it again. Okay. Yep. You guys tell science. He's sending her meet cartel Gore video
Yeah, that's me sounds bad. Yeah, please do not send Cheyenne any more of those videos
She is in contact with the authorities, but okay
Hey Daryl, how are you?
KT, Memphis, A, Money, Canada.
It says that people get kicked off a little like that.
Now it's just less people.
Yeah, like we're, it's not a big void in our hearts.
You know, the people that get timed out
and know everyone just, you know, cannot believe
they're provided for one day.
Okay.
Yeah, it's actually, it's a great thing.
It keeps the panel more calm and contained.
Okay, so let's do the private chat.
What's going on there?
Okay.
Yep.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
So, is there anybody like a reading?
If you like a reading, there's a little crystal ball emoji, so members will get priority,
but you can just go reading or as many cards, like a few cards.
I'll do some readings.
I'll stay up for maybe until 1 a.m., maybe, and hang out with you guys.
If you got like anything else, any requests, let me know.
Shout out KT. What's up guys?
Thank you guys
I think I have the best show best audience. I love this audience. Okay. Oh
spicy
Oh, you're eating your your soup noodles. Yeah
Really
I love spicy too
Not too spicy though. I've been to Thailand. They have really spicy
Yeah, I like to I like to sweat yeah, I do like to sweat when I eat. Are you guys like that you like it when it's really hot mm-hmm
I can't do it. I
Love it. I feel like it takes away the enjoyment of the food, but if you if you like you like it
Certain things like I only like it on certain like certain things, you know like certain foods that I think is just really good
Like noodles. I don't eat noodles without hot sauce, right? Like I won't eat them regular
I won't eat them with eggs or any of that. I just eat them on hot sauce, but it's not like super super hot, right?
It's like just enough
It's just a hot enough just to make you sweat a little bit the kid look it's fine
Okay, that's when people do this like a ghost chili the ghost pepper chili. Oh, yeah
I feel like you burn yourself. Yeah, that's like one of the that's not fun. It's one of the hottest. Yeah
Well, I bought some ghost pepper cheese before and I like cut it up on like a little cheese platter baited the guy
I gave it to this guy. He's a big bite of it. Here's the
This is really really spicy, especially if it sneaks up on you. Okay, we have hold on. Oh, I see you Canada drive coming under different names
I'm too smart. I don't know how I just found out
But I finally had one of the white castles with the jalapeno cheese on it with bacon. Oh my fucking god
Listen, that's it's fire. It's good. I was like that is usually I don't eat white castles that much
But when I do I'll just get you know playing white castles with or cheese white castles with pickles
But man, that's jalapeno cheese with bacon. Oh, yeah, that's fire
I was at the supermarket once so this was about like 10 years ago. I was at the supermarket buying some shit
I was in the veggie department.
I saw a bag of habaneros.
It was like, it was a fucking dollar.
I said, well, let me get these habaneros.
I like peppers.
Let me try this out.
I get the stupid idea in my head to make a steak
and put some habaneros on top of the steak, right?
So I cut up one, I cut up one habanero.
I slice it up, I put it on top of the steak.
I'm like, oh, this would be nice.
It'll give me a little kick.
After about fucking 20 minutes in the oven,
The whole kitchen was full of fucking smoke. All right, these habaneros they fucking smoked up into some toxic cloud
I walk in I open up the fucking oven door the fucking thing hits me right in the face
I start choking my eyes are fucking watering up everything. I'm on the fucking ground almost fucking just I can't see shit
You know these fucking I basically gasped myself with these fucking
This was one fucking pepper
Yeah, you have to be careful with some of those peppers Grim Reaper. What's up, baby? Hey God Grim Reaper's here
What are you gonna do? Who's Grim Reaper?
Grim Reaper. He's my buddy. He's
That's that phony Grim Reaper the old man. Yeah. Yeah, I know about him
He thinks he's somebody
You know why he gets mad because every time he kills somebody I bring him back to life
So, I mean, this is what we got going on
The little back of words life is the final word. I
Am the last one you will see okay, whatever dude
I'm in a network of Reapers, huh, huh, huh, whatever
You only exist cuz I let you
Yes, so don't play with that. I'll be back in just a minute, you guys. I had a hint of something real quick. I'll be right back.
Yeah, a random guy. It wasn't good.
I don't fuck with having arrows anymore.
God, sometimes you just don't come through. God, sometimes you just don't come through.
Do you need a woman to look after you hey Mondos here? Hello?
Whoa, what's up? Hello?
Who is this?
What up man, yeah, it's been it's
Ah, well, we thought your voice I
Don't know who that was it was Canada dry. It says hurdle shirts and it said Mondo Garmento
Yeah, that's good. I think I'm gonna ban that person in the studio. Bye Mondo
Adios
That was a demon I don't like one
Holy shit
You with the just some with a voice yeah, it was Canada dry the voice. Yeah, the voice went off
Revealed reveals. Yeah
Broke
Yeah
The little Canada Canada dry voice
Okay, I'll take off this area. Oh my gosh. Geez. She's Louise
Okay
Yeah, oh, let's see
Here's my little a little alleyway you want to go down the alley guys. Let's go down. Yeah, I love it
I love a nice alley in Chinatown. Yeah, I think we're in Chinatown or a little Tokyo
Little bit of both. I don't know. I don't know if that's a real Asian language, but interesting. Okay. Oh, there's all
They should there must be a YouTube channel that goes down to like CD areas
Like other kind of there are there's like well, there's a guy that went down to the sewers in Florida
They have these underground tunnel networks of these mole people that live in I mean not Florida in a Vegas
There's these underground tunnels
But uh, oh god, I wanted to ask you my opinion. I'm creating this
Kerojack, and I've created one card. What do you think is the card so far? I saw that. Yeah
You're gonna leave it like that. Are you gonna change the like the dude looks kind of normal
He looks too normal. I know I should make it look like me
Put something on his t-shirt if you can
It kind of looks like beta a little bit. Oh, yeah, I put a little like a logo on the t-shirt
I'll put a little you put a fool on his t-shirt like a like a jester
Hmm, good idea. Maybe I like the butterfly the cat and then the beta back there like laughing she's like
Collie kind of it's it's a oh
We put beta in the background, right?
Pretty fun. So which one do I get I get the son or do I get like the death card? I'll make you the emperor
Is that the best one?
Well, that's all the kings, you know, so it's pretty good or I can make you just a king of
Saying the Sun was the God card
Well, I mean that's the higher the Hierophant the Hierophant is like, you know, which is like a pope
It's kind of like the closest to god
But also the Sun too is like the Sun is most positive card in the deck. You can be associated with
You know an angel or oh god, it's the Sun is the rat angel Raphael. You know what, you know what?
Just give me the death card. I'll take the death card. You want death? Okay
Well, I was gonna give that to the green room for network
Don't know me. He asked first. I mean, it's only yes. I don't think he asked. No, I'm just kidding. He did
Yeah, I'm gonna make it I mean I make it it's called like the panel verse deck and it's gonna be like
You know, there's gonna be like a lot of us will be on the deck in the car
I got her on. Thanks, man. I put her on
She's on the big screen
See that ass in the fucking 75 inches
I'm gonna make
Sorry, let me let me mute it. Okay. Thank you so much
Fucking love the slob
Are you watching porn? Yeah, well almost it's this bald girl. Oh my god, why is she bald? I don't know. She's she seems middle-aged
She's drunk as shit and she's like
it's working on a couch
this is it for New Year's or no?
Oh yeah, I thought it was LD noser
Oh, I'm shocked
Okay, are you sure you're playing that on my show?
I'm not playing it, it's in the background
What is it?
Well, I know, but I hear it
It's okay, it's okay
Thank you so much
That is music
There is it there's a vacuum cleaner that is eight hundred fifty nine dollars. It is called the Omni robot vacuum and mop
18,000 PA suction Osmo roller. Have you heard an eight hundred dollar back? Can you imagine it's a one of those little like bucks to suck?
Yeah, that's a lot to suck. It's
more expensive than a you know
American hooker
Shit Canadian. I don't know has like but it says the it says meet the debauch
I mean, I don't even know what it does. It's a mobster floor. That's pretty good. Wow
Geez
I want them. I want a power mop like that eight hundred and fifty nine. That's so expensive
850 is stuck. I mean flirty will do it for like 40 bucks. No, yeah
Right, it's a joke people. It's a joke. Don't get offended. I'm offended for everybody
No, it's okay. What's your face?
Morpheme at it. Okay, so I'm looking at
the
At Amazon right now. Okay. I'm shouldn't be doing that. I should be paying attention to my show. Hello, God. Hey, how are you?
Oh, here I am. Hi
Yeah, okay, so what time are you Carolina Reaper's back today? So until 2 a.m.
So that's me a couple more hours. You're not in the dungeon of lost souls at the moment
But when I am you'll join me on panel. Okay, great from me for look forward to that
Job of the pizza hut. Oh joy. He's going to join us on the panel. I can't wait
I'm so excited
Who is joining us
God Reaper you like that artist yeah
Well, you know Justin, I mean, it's really in conjunction with AI, you know, human plus AI
Well, you're lying. You're lying boil. I know when you lie. He's lying. He says he's in love with it
He's not in love with that
Okay, okay sask. I know that's you. I know you there's nobody really named the quavis
Keisha or whatever the person's name is that she's a black lady with like powder all over her mouth
It's very racist and you're not getting on the show. Okay
Wait to your turn 24 hours, okay
Use that artist or yeah, I think with chat GPT it will continue to use that style
And it's like also it knows a lot about my show because I talked to it a lot until a lot of stuff
And so it knows all about a lot of people and we'll
Give suggestions. It's really cool. I really remember stuff. It's really really cool
That's how I do the songs that the AI songs
Use the like information I say in previous chats in the songs and stuff pretty cool
Okay, let's go Carter. Give me a break. Oh, give me a break because I should need one give me a break
Oh, yeah
Joey Lawrence started his career
Hey, hey, Joey Lawrence. Hey
Okay, you're James Cowboys with like a reading. Okay, I'm gonna pull out the
For Jamie, I'll do the rainbow taro
Fool a quick reading for miss Jamie. Jamie's
You know I'm recovering we went to miss Jamie the best recovery. I'm gonna do a little happy
Happy reading for you Jamie. Stay tuned over there. I'm gonna freak
This is the back of the car. Go ahead. You're doing reading. Go ahead. Yeah, this is the back of the car
Pretty cool, huh? Just hello. I'm so glad this deck is found as new home and really hope you like it
This is my most special project and it's years to make 2016 to 2022
It is inspired by love and queerness and so many emotions. Please enjoy. Okay, perfect for me. Okay love and queerness perfect. Okay, so
Jamie. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. And some advice. Okay. Jamie, like, so this is the, this is
going to be the four of cups. The four of cups is like some kind of boredom with what you
Happy with what she has they are upright cubs. They are good things, but she's being handed another one
What she's been really wanting for, you know, she's kind of turned down those she wants that okay, and then I have
Page of wands and so this is like the beginning of something something new for you that could grow into something
That will make you very passionate and things like that
I
Want to say the five of cubs this can indicate some regret about something though and so you want to make
Just make sure whatever you decide to do with this other opportunity that you're not...
Throwing away something else you have that you might really appreciate and like you might end up regretting it if you do and
You have the star card. This is the advice. The advice is just to shine shine your light also make a wish
You're also pouring it like a lot of a lot of love and good things. Oh, she's naked
Okay, but that the advice is they just keep the shine on shine on the little diamond. Okay shine on. Okay. Love you, Jamie
So we have mr. Let's see. Okay, okay
Canada dry
I know it's you. Okay, Mr. Mike. I know it's you. No, Mr. Mike is not that's not him
That's the dude from Chicago. No, it's this is I know I can see that fucking the registered account name and it's
Canada's right because there is a mister there is a mr. Mike from Chicago
Yeah, it's not the guy that dance with strips magic magic magic
Mr. Mike he has a lot of weed in itself
He's like me. Yeah, he's like me. I give it a speed. I got karate. Oh, it is him. Yeah, it's him
Pat marita. No, yeah, that's mr. Mike. That is mr. Mike
No, it's not. I don't need that. He just said the same thing we just said
Me look, I'm mr. Mike. I'm smoking weed
You said you're racist. We're not leading up to quabbas laverne. Okay, and that's those the quabbas
Yeah, the quabbas and then in this had initials JD for the official name and then I just opened mr. Mike
I said initials JD. Okay, that looks like not very convincing. It's okay. I'm not convinced
I'm just like a little I wasn't I was bored at in the morning, but not yesterday
Listen to this listen to this state turn went over to this girl's channel, right?
And these are the these are the comments. He's leaving on a channel while she's stripping on the couch
Rub your pussy on a piece of paper and mail it to me, you like that he wrote
Is that funny guys guys who's laughing I'm fucking out in them. I'm out in them on this fucking channel
Okay, but what he like because he put but he's out of himself if you've worked that in a chat, right?
You know nothing this yeah, he wrote in that chat. I'm saying everything. I'm all you need
What's had it which had is the end it's called our Queen Lilith 13. She's like
She's she black I rating all over the couch and drinking
Okay
Well, that's what I do and I have a good night. Oh, yeah, this video. Yeah, we saw that we don't want to see that again
You don't want to see it again. No, no
God not that kind of channel. Okay. Well
We're gonna make a decent channel out of this place
Okay, I'll be right back